<resources>
    <string name="app_name">WeLearn</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="test">Test</string>
    <string name="toolkits">Toolkits</string>
    <string name="materials">Materials</string>
    <string name="video">Video</string>
    <string name="tips">Tips</string>
    <string name="video_list">Video List</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="please_check_device_internet_connection">Please check device internet connection</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="finish">Finish</string>
    <string name="online">Online</string>
    <string name="offline">Offline</string>
    <string name="both">Both</string>
    <string name="dismiss">Dismiss</string>
    <string name="tips_online">Tips: Online</string>
    <string name="tips_offline">Tips: Offline</string>
    <string name="tips_online_offline">Tips: Online / Offline</string>
    <string name="test_result">Test Result</string>
    <string name="selection_of_content_n_n_the_teacher_describes_a_critical_incident_critical_incidents_are_tools_for_increasing_our_awareness_and_understanding_of_human_attitudes_expectations_behaviours_and_interactions_apedaile_schill_2008_the_critical_incident_could_range_from_not_being_time_conscious_respect_towards_authority_being_able_to_speak_one_s_mind_etc_one_way_of_identifying_such_incidents_as_proposed_by_the_developers_of_the_tool_fiedler_mitchell_triandis_1971_is_to_ask_the_students_about_intercultural_occurrences_or_events_that_highlighted_differences_in_attitude_or_behaviour_towards_members_of_other_cultures_such_events_could_be_pleasant_unpleasant_or_non_understandable_occurrences_this_is_an_example_of_a_critical_incident_as_described_by_the_developers_of_the_tool_this_example_was_posed_by_an_american_student_studying_in_thailand_the_student_indicated_that_he_had_had_a_number_of_appointments_with_thai_teachers_and_that_one_thing_that_bothered_him_considerably_was_the_lack_of_punctuality_of_the_thai_professors_he_asked_some_of_his_fellow_thai_students_if_they_were_angry_or_disturbed_over_the_tardiness_of_their_teachers_and_they_indicated_that_this_happened_rather_frequently_and_that_yes_it_disturbed_them_very_much_the_american_thought_about_saying_something_to_the_teacher_but_decided_against_it_when_the_thai_students_said_very_strongly_that_although_they_were_disturbed_they_would_never_show_their_feelings_to_their_professor_fiedler_mitchell_triandis_1971_n_n_use_the_content_to_simulate_an_encounter_n_n_the_next_step_is_for_the_teacher_to_contextualize_the_critical_incident_in_such_a_way_that_it_provides_the_answer_the_student_needs_the_developers_of_the_tool_describe_an_example_of_such_contextualization_one_day_a_thai_administrator_of_middle_academic_rank_kept_two_of_his_assistants_waiting_about_an_hour_for_an_appointment_the_assistants_although_very_angry_did_not_show_it_while_they_waited_when_the_administrator_walked_in_at_last_he_acted_as_if_he_were_not_late_he_made_no_apology_or_explanation_after_he_was_settled_in_his_office_he_called_his_assistants_in_and_they_all_began_working_on_the_business_for_which_the_administrator_had_set_the_meeting_source_fiedler_mitchell_triandis_1971_the_contextualization_reveals_the_cultural_response_of_locals_to_the_critical_incident_inorder_to_simulate_and_contextualize_critical_incidents_the_teacher_ought_to_be_conversant_with_the_culture_in_question_the_teacher_can_educate_his_herself_by_either_reading_or_watching_tv_documentaries_about_that_culture_n_n_provide_possible_feedback_and_alternatives_n_n_the_third_step_involves_the_teacher_leading_the_student_in_a_reflection_process_the_reflection_process_is_aimed_at_enabling_students_foreign_to_the_contextualized_culture_to_understand_the_cultural_basis_behind_the_critical_incident_it_also_enables_such_students_to_compare_their_culture_to_the_culture_being_contextualized_the_reflection_process_also_enables_the_students_to_correct_their_ethnocentric_errors_the_teacher_provides_a_set_of_one_correct_two_plausible_and_one_wrong_answers_to_assist_in_the_reflection_process_an_example_used_by_the_developers_on_the_tool_to_deal_with_the_american_student_s_dilemma_is_as_follows_n_n_o_the_thai_assistants_were_extremely_skillful_at_concealing_their_true_feelings_not_entirely_correct_n_n_o_the_thai_administrator_obviously_was_unaware_of_the_fact_that_he_was_an_hour_late_for_the_appointment_poor_choice_n_n_o_in_thailand_subordinates_are_required_to_be_polite_to_their_superiors_no_matter_what_happens_nor_what_their_rank_may_be_correct_n_n_o_clearly_since_no_one_commented_on_it_the_behavior_indicated_nothing_of_any_unusual_significance_to_any_of_the_thais_wrong_n_n_the_source_of_the_example_is_fiedler_mitchell_triandis_1971_students_are_given_time_to_reflect_and_provide_their_answers_the_teacher_then_provides_the_correct_answer_while_explaining_why_the_other_answers_were_either_not_totally_correct_or_wrong"><![CDATA[● Selection of content: \n \n The teacher describes a critical incident. “Critical incidents are tools for increasing our awareness and understanding of human attitudes, expectations, behaviours, and interactions” (Apedaile & Schill, 2008). The critical incident could range from not being time conscious, respect towards authority, being able to speak one\'s mind, etc. One way of identifying such incidents, as proposed by the developers of the tool (Fiedler, Mitchell, & Triandis, 1971), is to ask the students about intercultural occurrences or events that highlighted differences in attitude or behaviour towards members of other cultures. Such events could be pleasant, unpleasant or non-understandable occurrences. This is an example of a critical incident as described by the developers of the tool. This example was posed by an American student studying in Thailand. “The student indicated that he had had a number of appointments with Thai teachers, and that one thing that bothered him considerably was the lack of punctuality of the Thai professors. He asked some of his fellow Thai students if they were angry or disturbed over the tardiness of their teachers and they indicated that this happened rather frequently and that, yes, it disturbed them very much. The American thought about saying something to the teacher, but decided against it when the Thai students said very strongly that although they were disturbed they would never show their feelings to their professor”( (Fiedler, Mitchell, & Triandis, 1971)). \n \n ● Use the content to simulate an encounter: \n \n The next step is for the teacher to contextualize the critical incident in such a way that it provides the answer the student needs. The developers of the tool describe an example of such contextualization. “One day a Thai administrator of middle academic rank kept two of his assistants waiting about an hour for an appointment. The assistants, although very angry, did not show it while they waited. When the administrator walked in at last, he acted as if he were not late. He made no apology or explanation. After he was settled in his office, he called his assistants in and they all began working on the business for which the administrator had set the meeting” (source (Fiedler, Mitchell, & Triandis, 1971)). The contextualization reveals the cultural response of locals to the critical incident. Inorder to simulate and contextualize critical incidents, the teacher ought to be conversant with the culture in question. The teacher can educate his/herself by either reading or watching TV documentaries about that culture. \n \n ● Provide possible feedback and alternatives: \n \n The third step involves the teacher leading the student in a reflection process. The reflection process is aimed at enabling students, foreign to the contextualized culture, to understand the cultural basis behind the critical incident. It also enables such students to compare their culture to the culture being contextualized. The reflection process also enables the students to correct their ethnocentric errors. The teacher provides a set of one correct, two plausible and one wrong answers to assist in the reflection process. An example used by the developers on the tool to deal with the American student’s dilemma is as follows: \n \n o The Thai assistants were extremely skillful at concealing their true feelings. (not entirely correct). \n \n o The Thai administrator obviously was unaware of the fact that he was an hour late for the appointment (poor choice) \n \n o In Thailand, subordinates are required to be polite to their superiors, no matter what happens, nor what their rank may be. (correct) \n \n o Clearly, since no one commented on it, the behavior indicated nothing of any unusual significance to any of the Thais (wrong) \n \n The source of the example is (Fiedler, Mitchell, & Triandis, 1971) Students are given time to reflect and provide their answers. The teacher then provides the correct answer, while explaining why the other answers were either not totally correct or wrong.]]></string>
    <string name="offline_tool_1_implementation"><![CDATA[TOOL IMPLEMENTATION <br> <br> Activity 1: Preparation process <br> <br> ● Step 1: The teacher inscribes the quote cards with non-verbal behavior that often results in misunderstanding. The teacher can take inspiration for the non-verbal behaviours from critical incidents. The teacher can then inscribe these critical incidents in the quotecards. <br> <br> ● Step 2: The quote cards should consist of non-verbal behaviours from the different cultures represented in that multicultural classroom. <br> <br> ● Step 3: The teacher then divides the students into small groups, with each grouprepresenting students from different cultures. <br> <br> ● Step 4: the teacher introduces the students to the concept of the Iceberg metaphor (APA, 2021). <br> <br> Activity 2: Knowledge acquisition process <br> <br> ● Step 1: The teacher shares the quote cards to the individual small groups. <br> <br> ● Step 2: The students are instructed to read the cards and sort them into categories of their choosing. <br> <br> ● Step 3: Once sorted, each group must then name the categories as either acceptable behaviour or non-acceptable behaviour) explain the reasoning behind their choice. <br> <br> ● The teacher points out how the categories fit within the iceberg. In the explanation, the teacher explains how nob-verbal behavior (attitude), is hidden underneath the iceberg and the verbal behavior is above the iceberg and why it is hidden. <br> <br> Activity 2 helps the students to become sensitive and aware of acceptable and nonacceptable non-verbal behaviours from different cultural perspectives. A possible outcome is that some students might develop empathy towards their colleagues from other cultures. This opens up the possibility for behavior modification (Apedaile & Schill, 2008). <br> <br> ● Activity 3: Behaviour Modification process Students are provided with conscious behavior modification tips by the teacher. Such tips include. <br> <br> Conscious relay of non-verbal communication: Apedaile and Schill 2008 suggest telling the student thus. “Be aware of your own non-verbal communication” (Apedaile & Schill, 2008). This enables the student to understand that others may neither understand nor be aware of the non-verbal behaviour he or she exhibits. Hence, polite verbal communication might serve a better purpose than non-verbal communication that others do not understand. <br> <br> Selective judgement of non-verbal communication: Apedaile and Schill 2008 suggest telling the student thus. “Be aware of others’ behaviours and how these affect you. Unexpected and unfamiliar non-verbal behaviours can cause strong responses at an emotional level. Resist the temptation to make hasty, judgmental evaluations” (Apedaile & Schill, 2008). This helps the student not to be alert in always trying to interpret allnon- verbal communications. <br> <br> Conscious behaviour modification. Apedaile and Schill 2008 suggest telling the student thus. “Try to match your behaviour to those of the culture you are interacting with”. This involves the integration of the foreign student to the culture of the host country. The teacher should also inform the student thus,“Changing how you behave and how you understand others’ non-verbal communication is the key to successful non-verbal communication across cultures” (Apedaile & Schill, 2008). <br> <br> Do note that the onus for behaviour modification is on the student. The teacher only raises awareness.]]></string>
    <string name="offline_tool_9_implementation"><![CDATA[TOOL IMPLEMENTATION <br> <br> Activity 1: Preparation process <br> <br> ● Step 1: The teacher inscribes the quote cards with non-verbal behavior that often results in misunderstanding. The teacher can take inspiration for the non-verbal behaviours from critical incidents. The teacher can then inscribe these critical incidents in the quotecards. <br> <br> ● Step 2: The quote cards should consist of non-verbal behaviours from the different cultures represented in that multicultural classroom. <br> <br> ● Step 3: The teacher then divides the students into small groups, with each grouprepresenting students from different cultures. <br> <br> ● Step 4: the teacher introduces the students to the concept of the Iceberg metaphor (APA, 2021). <br> <br> Activity 2: Knowledge acquisition process <br> <br> ● Step 1: The teacher shares the quote cards to the individual small groups. <br> <br> ● Step 2: The students are instructed to read the cards and sort them into categories of their choosing. <br> <br> ● Step 3: Once sorted, each group must then name the categories as either acceptable behaviour or non-acceptable behaviour) explain the reasoning behind their choice. <br> <br> ● The teacher points out how the categories fit within the iceberg. In the explanation, the teacher explains how nob-verbal behavior (attitude), is hidden underneath the iceberg and the verbal behavior is above the iceberg and why it is hidden. <br> <br> Activity 2 helps the students to become sensitive and aware of acceptable and nonacceptable non-verbal behaviours from different cultural perspectives. A possible outcome is that some students might develop empathy towards their colleagues from other cultures. This opens up the possibility for behavior modification (Apedaile & Schill, 2008). <br> <br> ● Activity 3: Behaviour Modification process Students are provided with conscious behavior modification tips by the teacher. Such tips include. <br> <br> Conscious relay of non-verbal communication: Apedaile and Schill 2008 suggest telling the student thus. “Be aware of your own non-verbal communication” (Apedaile & Schill, 2008). This enables the student to understand that others may neither understand nor be aware of the non-verbal behaviour he or she exhibits. Hence, polite verbal communication might serve a better purpose than non-verbal communication that others do not understand. <br> <br> Selective judgement of non-verbal communication: Apedaile and Schill 2008 suggest telling the student thus. “Be aware of others’ behaviours and how these affect you. Unexpected and unfamiliar non-verbal behaviours can cause strong responses at an emotional level. Resist the temptation to make hasty, judgmental evaluations” (Apedaile & Schill, 2008). This helps the student not to be alert in always trying to interpret allnon- verbal communications. <br> <br> Conscious behaviour modification. Apedaile and Schill 2008 suggest telling the student thus. “Try to match your behaviour to those of the culture you are interacting with”. This involves the integration of the foreign student to the culture of the host country. The teacher should also inform the student thus,“Changing how you behave and how you understand others’ non-verbal communication is the key to successful non-verbal communication across cultures” (Apedaile & Schill, 2008). <br> <br> Do note that the onus for behaviour modification is on the student. The teacher only raises awareness.]]></string>
    <string name="tool_implementation_n_n_step_1_the_teacher_makes_the_choice_of_the_topic_of_discussion_for_the_student_a_critical_incident_that_has_cultural_undertones_is_a_good_choice_for_a_topic_n_n_step_2_the_teacher_divides_the_students_into_small_groups_of_at_least_2_students_n_n_step_3_the_teacher_instructs_the_students_on_the_following_rules_of_engagement_the_rules_stated_below_are_as_proposed_by_dresdner_2021_n_n_o_listen_with_openness_suspend_your_judgments_and_biases_and_listen_for_those_things_with_which_you_agree_as_well_as_those_you_might_challenge_n_n_o_listen_with_curiosity_engage_your_desire_to_learn_rather_than_to_try_to_fix_anything_n_n_o_listen_without_asking_questions_that_interrupt_the_speaker_jot_down_your_questions_and_save_them_for_later_n_n_o_listen_for_patterns_and_for_what_is_not_being_said_and_finally_q_n_n_o_listen_with_intention_what_do_you_intend_to_learn_or_do_with_the_information_you_ll_learn_n_n_source_of_quotes_dresdner_2021_things_to_note_for_the_students_as_proposed_by_dresdner_n_n_o_each_person_must_speak_once_before_anyone_can_speak_a_second_or_third_time_n_n_o_if_someone_asks_a_question_someone_else_must_answer_it_before_another_comment_can_be_made_n_n_source_of_quotes_dresdner_2021_n_n_step_4_the_teacher_should_identify_a_group_leader_who_will_ensure_that_the_rules_are_followed_n_n_step_5_as_one_student_in_the_group_speaks_on_a_topic_the_others_have_to_listen_attentively_and_intentionally_n_n_step_6_when_the_first_student_is_done_speaking_another_can_ask_a_follow_up_question_or_raise_comments_about_what_s_he_heard_n_n_step_7_steps_5_and_6_are_repeated_until_every_student_in_the_group_has_spoken_at_least_twice_or_for_a_specific_amount_of_time_n_n_step_8_the_group_leader_appointed_by_the_teacher_earlier_with_assistance_from_the_group_members_summarizes_the_conversation_and_identifies_patterns_or_insights_that_emerged_and_developed_in_the_course_of_the_dialogue_n_n_dresdner_2021_notes_that_teachers_should_not_be_alarmed_if_students_find_it_difficult_to_repeat_what_they_heard_in_context_from_their_peers_here_the_teacher_serves_as_a_bridge_to_help_the_student_pinpoint_what_they_misunderstood_furthermore_this_activity_should_be_practiced_continuously_to_help_the_student_perfect_their_active_listening_skills">TOOL IMPLEMENTATION \n \n ● Step 1: The teacher makes the choice of the topic of discussion for the student. A critical incident that has cultural undertones is a good choice for a topic. \n \n ● Step 2: The teacher divides the students into small groups of at least 2 students \n \n ● Step 3: The teacher instructs the students on the following rules of engagement: The rules stated below are as proposed by Dresdner, 2021. \n \n o “Listen with openness: suspend your judgments and biases and listen for those things with which you agree as well as those you might challenge;” \n \n o “Listen with curiosity: engage your desire to learn, rather than to try to “fix” anything;” \n \n o “Listen without asking questions that interrupt the speaker: jot down your questions and save them for later;” \n \n o “Listen for patterns and for what is not being said; and, finally,Q \n \n o “Listen with intention: what do you intend to learn or do with the information you’ll learn?” \n \n Source of quotes: Dresdner, 2021. Things to note for the students as proposed by Dresdner. \n \n o “Each person must speak once before anyone can speak a second (or third) time”. \n \n o “If someone asks a question, someone else must answer it before another comment can be made”. \n \n Source of quotes: Dresdner, 2021. \n \n ● Step 4: The teacher should identify a group leader who will ensure that the rules are followed. \n \n ● Step 5: As one student in the group speaks on a topic, the others have to listen attentively and intentionally. \n \n ● Step 6: when the first student is done speaking, another can ask a follow up question or raise comments about what s/he heard. \n \n ● Step 7: Steps 5 and 6 are repeated until every student in the group has spoken at least twice, or for a specific amount of time. \n \n ● Step 8: The group leader appointed by the teacher earlier, with assistance from the group members, summarizes the conversation and identifies patterns or insights that emerged and developed in the course of the dialogue. \n \n Dresdner(2021) notes that teachers should not be alarmed if students find it difficult to repeat what they heard in context from their peers. Here the teacher serves as a bridge to help the student pinpoint what they misunderstood. Furthermore, this activity should be practiced continuously to help the student perfect their active listening skills.</string>
    <string name="tool_implementation_n_n_described_is_the_implementation_process_as_extracted_from_sarah_apedaile_and_lenina_schill_2008_n_n_activity_1_imagining_prejudice_n_n_step_1_ask_a_student_to_draw_an_alien_face_on_the_board_or_flip_chart_n_n_step_2_you_can_also_draw_the_alien_face_yourself_n_n_step_3_invite_students_to_describe_what_had_been_drawn_on_the_board_or_flip_chart_n_n_step_4_once_all_students_have_described_what_they_see_the_teacher_then_asks_the_following_questions_n_n_how_do_we_know_all_this_when_we_have_never_seen_the_character_before_apedaile_schill_2008_or_how_do_we_know_all_this_when_we_have_never_met_this_character_before_apedaile_schill_2008_n_n_then_ask_what_are_we_doing_apedaile_schill_2008_it_is_likely_that_a_student_will_identify_their_action_as_prejudice_if_no_student_provides_the_correct_answer_the_teacher_then_reveals_the_action_as_prejudice_n_n_step_5_the_teacher_then_explains_prejudice_by_exploring_its_latin_root_praejudicium_praejudicium_means_an_opinion_or_judgement_formed_without_due_examination_apedaile_schill_2008_the_teacher_then_asks_the_participants_n_n_has_anyone_ever_thought_or_said_something_about_you_that_was_not_true_apedaile_schill_2008_n_n_have_you_ever_thought_or_said_something_about_someone_else_that_wasn_t_true_based_on_the_person_s_appearance_origin_sexual_orientation_apedaile_schill_2008_n_n_activity_2_imagining_stereotyping_n_n_step_1_the_teacher_then_asks_the_participants_to_think_about_the_character_s_neighbourhood_or_planet_pretend_that_everyone_in_the_neighbourhood_is_exactly_the_same_and_share_their_thoughts_on_what_they_think_about_the_imaginary_neighbourhood_n_n_step_2_after_students_share_their_thoughts_the_teacher_then_ask_this_question_based_on_the_thoughts_shared_by_the_students_n_n_what_are_we_doing_when_we_say_this_being_one_of_the_answers_given_by_the_student_it_is_likely_that_a_student_will_identify_their_action_as_stereotyping_if_no_student_provides_the_correct_answer_the_teacher_then_reveals_the_action_as_stereotyping_the_teacher_explains_what_stereotyping_is_and_proceeds_to_ask_the_participants_about_their_experience_with_stereotyping_they_could_be_the_stereotyping_they_experienced_or_that_which_was_directed_at_a_group_of_people_or_individuals_from_a_particular_culture_n_n_activity_3_imagining_discrimination_n_n_step_1_the_teacher_asks_the_participants_to_imagine_that_the_character_drawn_on_the_flip_chart_or_board_comes_into_class_and_the_students_refuse_access_to_the_character_as_a_result_of_their_culture_race_or_religion_the_teacher_then_asks_what_is_that_it_is_likely_that_a_student_will_identify_their_action_as_discrimination_if_not_student_provides_the_correct_answer_the_teacher_then_reveals_the_action_as_discrimination_the_teacher_explains_what_discreamination_means_and_proceeds_to_ask_the_participants_about_their_experience_with_discrimination_they_could_be_the_stereotyping_they_experienced_or_that_which_was_directed_at_a_group_of_people_or_individuals_from_a_particular_culture_n_n_activity_4_exchange_of_experience_n_n_step_1_as_a_facilitator_share_stories_of_prejudice_discrimination_and_stereotyping_that_you_have_experienced_and_how_you_felt_this_is_necessary_to_enable_the_students_to_open_up_to_share_their_experience_n_n_step_2_ask_the_students_to_share_their_own_stories_of_prejudice_discrimination_and_stereotyping_and_how_the_felt_during_the_experience_this_should_not_be_a_shaming_experience_for_any_student_n_n_step_3_a_good_way_of_wrapping_up_the_session_is_to_read_the_local_charter_of_rights_and_freedoms_to_the_students_it_is_good_practice_to_ensure_they_have_a_copy_n_n_it_is_important_that_the_teacher_is_conversant_with_the_level_of_language_proficiency_needed_by_their_learners_in_order_to_gain_the_most_benefit_from_this_activity_apedaile_schill_2008"><![CDATA[TOOL IMPLEMENTATION \n \n Described is the implementation process as extracted from Sarah Apedaile and Lenina Schill (2008). \n \n Activity 1: Imagining prejudice \n \n ● Step 1: Ask a student to draw an alien face on the board or flip chart. \n \n ● Step 2: You can also draw the alien face yourself. \n \n ● Step 3: Invite students to describe what had been drawn on the board or flip chart. \n \n ● Step 4: Once all students have described what they see, the teacher then asks the following questions, \n \n “How do we know all this when we have never seen the character before?” (Apedaile & Schill, 2008) or “How do we know all this when we have never met this character before?” (Apedaile & Schill, 2008) \n \n Then ask, “What are we doing?” (Apedaile & Schill, 2008). It is likely that a student will identify their action as “prejudice”. If no student provides the correct answer, the teacher then reveals the action as prejudice. \n \n ● Step 5. The teacher then explains prejudice by exploring its Latin root praejudicium. Praejudicium means an opinion or judgement formed without due examination (Apedaile & Schill, 2008). The teacher then asks the participants: \n \n “Has anyone ever thought or said something about you that was not true?” (Apedaile & Schill, 2008) \n \n “Have you ever thought or said something about someone else that wasn’t true, based on the person’s appearance/origin/sexual orientation?” (Apedaile & Schill, 2008). \n \n Activity 2 Imagining Stereotyping \n \n ● Step 1: The teacher then asks the participants to think about the character’s neighbourhood (or planet!); pretend that everyone in the neighbourhood is exactly the same and share their thoughts on what they think about the imaginary Neighbourhood. \n \n Step 2: After students share their thoughts, the teacher then ask this question based on the thoughts shared by the students: \n \n “What are we doing when we say this (being one of the answers given by the student)?” It is likely that a student will identify their action as “stereotyping”. If no student provides the correct answer, the teacher then reveals the action as stereotyping. The teacher explains what stereotyping is and proceeds to ask the participants about their experience with stereotyping. They could be the stereotyping they experienced or that which was directed at a group of people or individuals from a particular culture. \n \n Activity 3: Imagining discrimination \n \n ● Step 1: The teacher asks the participants to imagine that the character drawn on the flip chart or board comes into class and the students refuse access to the character as a result of their culture, race, or religion. The teacher then asks, “What is that?” It is likely that a student will identify their action as “discrimination”. If not student provides the correct answer, the teacher then reveals the action as discrimination. The teacher explains what discreamination means and proceeds to ask the participants about their experience with discrimination. They could be the stereotyping they experienced or that which was directed at a group of people or individuals from a particular culture. \n \n Activity 4: Exchange of experience \n \n ● Step 1: As a facilitator, share stories of prejudice, discrimination and stereotyping that you have experienced and how you felt. This is necessary to enable the students to open up to share their experience. \n \n ● Step 2: Ask the students to share their own stories of prejudice, discrimination and stereotyping and how the felt during the experience. This should not be a shaming experience for any student. \n \n ● Step 3: A good way of wrapping up the session is to read the local charter of rights and freedoms to the students. It is good practice to ensure they have a copy. \n \n It is important that the teacher is conversant with the level of language proficiency needed by their learners in order to gain the most benefit from this activity (Apedaile & Schill, 2008).]]></string>

    <string name="welearn_website">&lt;u&gt;WeLearn Website&lt;/u&gt;</string>
    <string name="material1">“Neighbourness” competences: A literature Review Report – WeLearn Intellectual Output 1 / Activity 1</string>
    <string name="material2">Intercultural Communication and Neighbourness Training Toolkit</string>
    <string name="material3">Intercultural Communication and Neighbourness Training Online Toolkit</string>
    <string name="material4">The Student Evaluations on Training Toolkit</string>
    <string name="str_about">The world is getting more and more global, which is transforming a traditional classroom into multicultural learning environment. Different cultures have different ways to learn and receive data, thus the commonly used teaching methods might not work. To increase positive learning outcomes in the multicultural learning environment, the WeLearn project was developed. \n\nWeLearn is a project that aims to find ways to support teachers and students in multicultural learning environments. To achieve this outcome, the project studied the Neighbourness concept and used the findings to develop offline and online toolkits for teachers. \n\nThe WeLearn consortium has overall six European partners: \n\nTampere University - \nhttps://www.tuni.fi/en \n\nRiga Technical University - \nhttps://www.rtu.lv/en \n\nFilm University Babelsberg - \nhttps://www.filmuniversitaet.de/ \n\nAalborg University - \nhttps://www.en.aau.dk/ \n\nCatholic University of Sacred Heart - \nhttps://www.unicatt.eu/ \n\nSuleyman Demirel University - \nhttps://w3.sdu.edu.tr/ \n\nWeLearn project is led by Tampere University, while Riga Technical University is in charge of the technical development of the WeLearn application. \n\nThis project has been funded with support from the European Commission. The author is solely in charge for project outcomes and the commission is not responsible for any projecting outcomes. \n\nWeLearn team respects users’ privacy. Thus, it is important to note that the WeLearn application does not collect, store or share any data with third parties.</string>

    <string name="offline_tools_title1">TOOL 1. (Offline Tool) \nNon-verbal cultural communication cues</string>
    <string name="offline_tools_title2">TOOL 2. (Offline Tool) \nActive listening: small group activity</string>
    <string name="offline_tools_title3">TOOL 3. (Offline Tool) \nThe cultural assimilator</string>
    <string name="offline_tools_title4">TOOL 4. (Offline Tool) \nOvercoming cultural stereotypes</string>
    <string name="offline_tools_title5">TOOL 5. (Offline Tool) \nRelating prejudice, stereotype and discrimination</string>
    <string name="offline_tools_title6">TOOL 6. (Offline Tool) \n Jigsaw classroom</string>
    <string name="offline_tools_title7">TOOL 7. (Offline Tool) \nSelf-reflection assignment based on ‘Feeling Italian’ book</string>
    <string name="offline_tools_title8">TOOL 8. (Offline Tool) \nSmall research groups and ethnographic interviews</string>
    <string name="offline_tools_title9">TOOL 9. (Offline Tool) \nStorytelling using silent books</string>
    <string name="offline_tools_title10">TOOL 10. (Offline Tool) \nCollaborative online international learning</string>
    <string name="online_tools_title1">TOOL 11. (Online Tool) \nHow to be a_________?</string>
    <string name="online_tools_title2">TOOL 12. (Online Tool) \nCollaborative Case analysis with Flinga</string>
    <string name="online_tools_title3">TOOL 13. (Online Tool) \nSensitising with Web Questionnaires</string>
    <string name="online_tools_title4">TOOL 14. (Online Tool) \nNeighborness Storytelling Workshop</string>
    <string name="online_tools_title5">TOOL 15. (Online Tool) \nMIPPS: Method of Intercultural Project Presentation and Socialising</string>
    <string name="online_tools_title6">TOOL 16. (Online Tool) \nAudience Exploration</string>


    <string name="offline_tools_description_1"><![CDATA[The teacher’s goal in using this tool is to develop the intercultural competence of students. The tool enables the teacher to deal with challenges related to misunderstanding of cultural disposition towards others, asymmetric communications and differences in cultural behavioural norms. <br> <br> The setting for the implementation of this tool is a multicultural classroom and the students have to be clustered in multicultural groups for the activity. <br> <br> The teacher decides the duration and the resources needed for the activity. This demands creativity and innovation on the side of the teacher. <br> <br> TOOL DESCRIPTION <br> <br> The Jigsaw classroom method involves dividing the class up in groups of five or six students. Each member of a group is assigned some unique, cultural information of one of the student groups, to learn that must later be shared with the other members of that group in order for the group to achieve its common goal (Aronson & Patnoe, 2011). Such information could be on the asymmetric communications etc as mentioned earlier. An example of such information could be on “conversational norms”. In sum, this offers the opportunity for cooperative learning about a particular culture. <br> <br> USEFULNESS OF THE TOOL <br> <br> This tool helps in fostering cooperative learning in classrooms (Santos Rego & Moledo, 2005). It has been used to promote intercultural attitude and behavior of students in multicultural classrooms (Santos Rego & Moledo, 2005). The tool enables students in multicultural classrooms to acquire knowledge and skills relevant for them to work together without friction in multicultural groups. <br> <br> REFERENCE FOR THE TOOL: <br> <br> For more information about the tool visit: https://www.jigsaw.org/]]></string>
    <string name="offline_tools_description_2"><![CDATA[The teacher’s goal in using the tool is to develop the intercultural competence and global citizenship competence of the students. The tool enables the student to deal with all the challenges mentioned in module two, chapter one. This is because the self-reflection process results in the foreign student developing his or her cultural self-awareness to their host culture within the context of the challenges mentioned in module two, chapter one. In the process, they gain new understanding on how the wider world works within the context of their host. <br> <br> The setting for the implementation of this tool could either be an activity such as a seminar, a workshop or group activity within a multicultural classroom. The teacher decides the duration and the resources needed for the activity. This demands creativity and innovation on the side of the teacher. <br> <br> TOOL DESCRIPTION <br> <br> The implementation of this tool requires a book that describes what it means to integrate into the host society. Prof. Maura di Mauro has implemented this tool in Italy using the book “Feeling Italian”. The self-reflection tool consists of a list of 10 questions, which enables foreign students to become self-aware of the Italian cultural environment they find themselves. The tool implementation will be based on the Italian example. A teacher in any other country can contextualize this tool in their local culture, using a similar book from that culture. <br> <br> USEFULNESS OF THE TOOL <br> <br> This tool enables foreign students to conduct a self-assessment of their level of integration in the host society. This tool enables the student to develop further their cultural awareness to the host society. The tool also enables the student to understand how the host society operates in terms of cultural values, philosophy and norms. <br> <br> REFERENCES TO THE TOOL <br> <br> For more information, read: Self-Reflection Assignment based on Feeling Italian book by Prof. Maura Di Mauro – Intercultural Management Università Cattolica del Sacro Cuore, Piacenza. <br> <br> https://centerforinterculturaldialogue.files.wordpress.com/2021/02/icd-exercise-2-dimauro.pdf]]></string>
    <string name="offline_tools_description_3"><![CDATA[The teacher’s goal in using the tool is to develop the intercultural of the students. The tool enables the student to deal with all the challenges mentioned in module two, chapter one. This tool also aids in the students to gain knowledge that will influence their intercultural skill and attitude towards persons from other cultures. The difference between this tool and tool number two is that students actually go out to explore intercultural problems. Such problems could be any of those mentioned in module two, chapter one. <br> <br> The setting for the implementation of this tool is within and outside the multicultural classroom. The students receive instructions on how to implement the tool from the teacher in a classroom. However, they explore the problem outside the classroom in clusters of multicultural groups. The teacher decides the duration and the resources needed for the activity. This, as in the previous tool, demands creativity and innovation on the side of the teacher. <br> <br> TOOL DESCRIPTION <br> <br> One approach towards developing the intercultural self-awareness of students is to explore issues related to other cultures represented in the class. Students can be involved in small research groups where they have to investigate a certain issue through a small cross-sectional research project. Examples of topics that could be researched include differences in pedagogical approaches in their country of origin as opposed to their host country; the role of informal education in a particular culture; and or cultural communication patterns. After researching the topics, the students can produce interactive presentations as well as document what they have learnt in the process. <br> <br> USEFULNESS OF THE TOOL <br> <br> This tool enables the student to develop cultural sensitivity and cultural awareness via collaborative cross-sectional research. They can conduct the research by either reviewing literature or reaching out to persons from the target culture to interview them. Unlike the Jigsaw classroom, this activity goes beyond the boundaries of the classroom.]]></string>
    <string name="offline_tools_description_4"><![CDATA[The teacher’s goal in using the tool is to develop the intercultural competence of the student. The tool helps students recognize and to do away with stereotypes. The tool is very helpful for dealing with challenges arising from misunderstanding of cultural disposition towards others. These are challenges that could arise as a result of ethnocentrism, stereotyping, etc. The setting for the implementation of this tool is within and outside the multicultural classroom. In the multicultural classroom, a separate hour for the activity within a course should be set aside, if it is to be implemented within a course. The implementation of the tool outside the classroom could be in the form of an intercultural competence workshop or training session. <br> <br> The teacher decides the duration, scope and the resources needed for the activity. However, the teacher should ensure that students are provided with writing materials for the exercise. The teacher should also provide a white board or a marker for illustrations. The teacher can also decide to be creative on how to approach the interaction. <br> <br> TOOL DESCRIPTION <br> <br> This tool provides a 4-step process that enables students to unlearn cultural stereotypes. The 3-step process enables the student to become self-aware of the stereotypes they possess; evaluate the extent by which they stereotype; and make a conscious effort to avoid stereotyping. This tool only works if the student is willing to let go of cultural stereotyping. If the student is unwilling to make an effort, then this tool is not relevant. Howard, Ross, a diversity-training consultant developed this tool. <br> <br> USEFULNESS OF THE TOOL <br> <br> This tool is relevant in a class where cultural stereotypes and ethnocentrism exist. The tool assists the student to become self-aware of his/her cultural stereotypes and to unlearn these stereotypes. <br> <br> REFERENCE TO THE TOOL <br> <br> For more information: See . <br> <br> https://culturalmisconceptions.wordpress.com/2013/03/22/overcoming-cultural-stereotypes/]]></string>
    <string name="offline_tools_description_5"><![CDATA[The teacher’s goal in using the tool is to develop the intercultural and global citizenship competence of the student. The tool is suitable for dealing with the challenges outlined in module two, chapter one. The tool provides the knowledge needed by students to understand not just persons from other cultures but the culture of the person as well. The tool also enables the students to develop their intercultural awareness and sensitivity competences. <br> <br> The setting for the implementation of this tool is within a multicultural classroom. The teacher determines the duration of the activity. However, 45 minutes is ideal. <br> <br> The resources needed for the activity includes a book consisting of very short stories about a particular culture or nationality. The book should be available for all students in the class. <br> <br> TOOL DESCRIPTION <br> <br> This tool enables dialogue and exchange between students. It enables students to understand how their peers from different cultures feel, reflect, interpret and evaluate a single story. The group of students who use this tool will get to learn new words, grammar, narrative structures; understand the life experience of their peers from other countries, cities, places, people etc; and reflect on their life. The students will learn via self-reflection and active listening. <br> <br> USEFULNESS OF THE TOOL <br> <br> This tool developed the Intercultural awareness and cultural sensitivity of students. It also helps the student to learn about as well as understand the wider world. Furthermore, it helps the student to understand how to interact with people from different cultures. <br> <br> REFERENCE TO THE TOOL <br> <br> The tool is extracted from Bupnet.eu]]></string>
    <string name="offline_tools_description_6"><![CDATA[The teacher’s goal in using the tool is to develop directly and indirectly the intercultural and Neighbourliness competence of the student respectively. The tool is suitable for dealing with the challenges outlined in module two, chapter one. The tool exposes students to cultural differences using critical incidents that could prevent neighbourliness because of lack of cultural sensitivity and awareness in a multicultural classroom. The setting for the implementation of this tool is within a multicultural classroom. The teacher decides on the duration and resources needed for the activity. <br> <br> TOOL DESCRIPTION <br> <br> This tool was developed at the University of Illinois. It consists of a set of critical incidents used in order to understand the reasons for misunderstanding between multicultural groups. The instructor inorder to simulate real life conflict incidents that depict the source of conflict in multicultural groups uses the critical incidents. The lessons from the simulation helps students become self aware and knowledgeable of the behaviour patterns of other cultures. Thus reducing misunderstanding and providing room for neighbourly initiatives based on the knowledge acquired from this tool. <br> <br> USEFULNESS OF THE TOOL <br> <br> The tool is useful in preventing or solving conflicts that arise as a result of either lack of cultural awareness. The tool also breaks down the barriers that impede acts of Neighbourliness in a multicultural classroom. <br> <br> REFERENCE TO THE TOOL <br> <br> The example extracted from the developers of the tool is meant to serve as an inspiration in the simulation process. For more information about this tool, see <br> <br> https://apps.dtic.mil/dtic/tr/fulltext/u2/704517.pdf <br> <br> https://www.norquest.ca/NorquestCollege/media/pdf/centres/intercultural/CriticalIncidentsBooklet.pdf]]></string>
    <string name="offline_tools_description_7"><![CDATA[The teacher’s goal in using the tool is to develop the intercultural competence of the student. The tool is suitable for dealing with the challenges pertaining to prejudice, sterotypes and discrimination. These challenges could be as a result of any of the problems outlined in in module two, chapter one. The developes the sensitivity of students toward prejudice, sterotypes and discriminative behaviours they exhibit either consciously or unconsciously. The setting for the implementation of this tool is within a multicultural classroom. The teacher decides on the duration. In principle, this is not an activity that should take more than an hour. However, there could be circumstances due to class size where it might take longer to implement this tool. Hence, the teacher can use his or her discretion. To implement this tool, the teacher has to provide, the following: <br> <br> ● Flip charts <br> <br> ● Drawing materials (pens, board markers). <br> <br> ● Local charter of human rights and freedoms. <br> <br> TOOL DESCRIPTION <br> <br> The aim of this tool is to enable the student’s self-awareness and implications of sterotyping, predjudice and discrimination (Apedaile & Schill, 2008). A fictional character and a cultural identity is used. In order to enable the tool to achieve its objective, the teacher should be aware of the level of trust they have from the students and adapt the exercises to suit them to avoid offending some students. <br> <br> USEFULNESS OF THE TOOL <br> <br> This tool will assist students in becoming self aware of the meaning and implication of stereotyping, prejudice, and discrimination. It is useful in the development of cultural sensitivity of students. However, this tool should only be facilitated by teachers who themselves are culturally sensitive to avoid chaos. <br> <br> REFERENCE TO THE TOOL <br> <br> For more information on this tool, visit: <br> <br> https://www.norquest.ca/NorquestCollege/media/pdf/centres/intercultural/CriticalIncidentsBooklet.pdf]]></string>
    <string name="offline_tools_description_8"><![CDATA[The teacher’s goal in using the tool is to develop the intercultural and global citizenship competence of students. The tool is suitable for dealing with challenges emanating from the misunderstanding of verbal and non-verbal cues in the course of an interaction in multicultural classrooms. <br> <br> The setting for the implementation of this tool is within a multicultural classroom. The teacher decides on the duration. Just as is the case for tool 7, this is not an activity that should take more than an hour. The resources needed are quote cards inscribed with non-verbal behavior from different cultures. <br> <br> TOOL DESCRIPTION <br> <br> This tool educates the students on how to avoid misattribution, sending the wrong signal, missing reading body languages and the misunderstanding of context arising from non-verbal communications. The tool promotes behaviour modification based on knowledge acquisition. <br> <br> USEFULNESS OF TOOLS <br> <br> This tool will be useful in equipping students on ways in which they can gain knowledge as well as modify their behavior in order to transmit decodable verbal cues and decode other verbal cues. The tool will be useful in reducing conflicts that arise as a result of non-verbal communications in student groups in a multicultural classroom. It also helps the willing students to develop their global citizenship competences. <br> <br> REFERENCE TO THE TOOL <br> <br> For more information on this tool, visit <br> <br> https://www.norquest.ca/NorquestCollege/media/pdf/centres/intercultural/CriticalIncidentsBooklet.pdf]]></string>
    <string name="offline_tools_description_9"><![CDATA[The teacher’s goal in using the tool is to develop the intercultural and global citizenship competence of students. The tool is suitable for dealing with challenges related to language barrier. However, the tool is only useful if the parties involved can sustain conversation in a common language. In this case the language of the host culture. The setting for the implementation of this tool is within a multicultural classroom. The teacher decides on the duration and the resources needed in the implementation of the tool. <br> <br> TOOL DESCRIPTION <br> <br> This is a tool developed by Lisa Dresdner, Ph.D.From Norwalk Community College (Dresdner, 2021). This tool enables students to develop their active listening skills. Active listening is an intercultural communication and neighbourliness competence. <br> <br> USEFULNESS OF THE TOOL <br> <br> The tool trains students to become active listeners. Active listening develops the student’s ability to pay attention to what their colleagues from other cultures say and not what they think their colleagues are saying. It is one way a student can learn about a foreign or local colleague from experience and not from a stereotypical point of view. <br> <br> REFERENCE TO THE TOOL <br> <br> For more information on this too, visit https://www.bellarmine.edu/docs/defaultsource/faculty-development-docs/06-active-listening.pdf?sfvrsn=1db29481_2]]></string>
    <string name="offline_tools_description_10"><![CDATA[This tool is different from the other. This is because it is a university initiative rather than an initiative a teacher can facilitate on their own. However, it is a tool that promotes the global citizenship of students. <br> <br> Using the Collaborative Online International Learning (COIL) model, faculties of at least two different institutions can partner to create joint courses, classes, or learning modules, to enhance students’ distant collaboration. For instances, universities can partner to create virtual learning activities, and to use common available social medias and exchange tools - such as Facebook, Google Groups, or discussion forum tools in the institution’s learning management system - to involve students of both institutions on topics such as diversity and social inequality (e.g., Kinginger, Gourvès-Hayward, & Simpson 1999; Liaw 2006; O’Dowd 2003; Thorne 2003; Custer, & Tuominen, 2017). Examples of students’ instructions are: write a 5+ line paragraph; present an example of how your society promotes particular gender roles in family and/or work, and explain how. Students can also be invited to attach visual “cultural” images that support, promote, and encourage the message they are presenting. Students of both institutions are then invited by their instructors to share what they wrote and prepared by using COIL modality. Instructors’ role during the virtual collaboration is to facilitate exchanges and discussions among students from different institutions, encouraging a cultural perspective understanding on global issues, and facilitating going beyond stereotypes and prejudices.]]></string>
    <string name="jh"><![CDATA[This tool is different from the other. This is because it is a university initiative rather than an initiative a teacher can facilitate on their own. However, it is a tool that promotes the global citizenship of students. <br> <br> Using the Collaborative Online International Learning (COIL) model, faculties of at least two different institutions can partner to create joint courses, classes, or learning modules, to enhance students’ distant collaboration. For instances, universities can partner to create virtual learning activities, and to use common available social medias and exchange tools - such as Facebook, Google Groups, or discussion forum tools in the institution’s learning management system - to involve students of both institutions on topics such as diversity and social inequality (e.g., Kinginger, Gourvès-Hayward, & Simpson 1999; Liaw 2006; O’Dowd 2003; Thorne 2003; Custer, & Tuominen, 2017). Examples of students’ instructions are: write a 5+ line paragraph; present an example of how your society promotes particular gender roles in family and/or work, and explain how. Students can also be invited to attach visual “cultural” images that support, promote, and encourage the message they are presenting. Students of both institutions are then invited by their instructors to share what they wrote and prepared by using COIL modality. Instructors’ role during the virtual collaboration is to facilitate exchanges and discussions among students from different institutions, encouraging a cultural perspective understanding on global issues, and facilitating going beyond stereotypes and prejudices.]]></string>



    <string name="offline_tool1_implementation"><![CDATA[<b>TOOL IMPLEMENTATION</b>
    <br><br>The setting for the implementation of this tool is within a multicultural classroom.  The teacher decides on the duration. As is the case for tool 5, this is not an activity that should take more than an hour. The resources needed are quote cards inscribed with non-verbal behaviour from different cultures.
<br><br>	<b>Activity 1:</b> Preparation process
<br><br><b>Step 1:</b>	The teacher inscribes the quote cards with non-verbal behaviour that often results in misunderstanding. The teacher can take inspiration for the non-verbal behaviours from critical incidents. The teacher can then inscribe these critical incidents in the quote cards.
<br><br><b>Step 2:</b>	The quote cards should consist of non-verbal behaviours from the different cultures represented in that multicultural classroom.
<br><br><b>Step 3:</b>	The teacher then divides the students into small groups, with each group-representing students from different cultures.
<br><br><b>Step 4:</b>	The teacher introduces the students to the concept of the Iceberg metaphor (APA, 2021).
	<br><br><b>Activity 2:</b> Knowledge acquisition process
<br><br><b>Step 1:</b>	The teacher shares the quote cards to the individual small groups.
<br><br><b>Step 2:</b>	The students are instructed to read the cards and sort them into categories of their choosing.
<br><br><b>Step 3:</b>	Once sorted, each group must then name the categories as either acceptable behaviour or non-acceptable behaviour) explain the reasoning behind their choice.

<br><br>The teacher points out how the categories fit within the iceberg. In the explanation, the teacher explains how non-verbal behaviour (attitude), is hidden underneath the iceberg and the verbal behaviour is above the iceberg and why it is hidden.
<br><br>Activity 2 helps the students to become sensitive and aware of acceptable and non-acceptable non-verbal behaviours from different cultural perspectives. A possible outcome is that some students might develop empathy towards their colleagues from other cultures. This opens up the possibility for behaviour modification (Apedaile & Schill, 2008).
]]></string>
    <string name="offline_tool2_implementation"><![CDATA[<b>TOOL IMPLEMENTATION</b>
    <br><br>The setting for the implementation of this tool is within a multicultural classroom.  The teacher decides on the duration and the resources needed in the implementation of the tool.
<br><br><b>Step 1:</b>	The teacher makes the choice of the topic of discussion for the student. A critical incident that has cultural undertones is a good choice for a topic.
<br><br><b>Step 2:</b>	The teacher divides the students into small groups of at least 2 students.
<br><br><b>Step 3:</b>	The teacher instructs the students on the following rules of engagement: The rules stated below are as proposed by Dresdner, 2021.
<br><br>●	“Listen with openness: suspend your judgments and biases and listen for those things with which you agree as well as those you might challenge;”
<br><br>●	“Listen with curiosity: engage your desire to learn, rather than to try to “fix” anything;”
<br><br>●	“Listen without asking questions that interrupt the speaker: jot down your questions and save them for later;”
<br><br>●	“Listen for patterns and for what is not being said; and, finally, Q;
<br><br>●	“Listen with intention: what do you intend to learn or do with the information you’ll learn?” (Source of quotes: Dresdner, 2021.)
<br><br>Things to note for the students as proposed by Dresdner:
<br><br>●	“Each person must speak once before anyone can speak a second (or third) time”.
<br><br>●	“If someone asks a question, someone else must answer it before another comment can be made”. (Source of quotes: Dresdner, 2021.)
<br><br><b>Step 4:</b>	The teacher should identify a group leader who will ensure that the rules are followed.
<br><br><b>Step 5:</b>	As one student in the group speaks on a topic, the others have to listen attentively and intentionally.
<br><br><b>Step 6:</b>	When the first student is done speaking, another can ask a follow up question or raise comments about what s/he heard.
<br><br><b>Step 7:</b>	Steps 5 and 6 are repeated until every student in the group has spoken at least twice, or for a specific amount of time.
<br><br><b>Step 8:</b>	The group leader appointed by the teacher earlier, with assistance from the group members, summarises the conversation and identifies patterns or insights that emerged and developed in the course of the dialogue.

<br><br>Dresdner (2021) notes that teachers should not be alarmed if students find it difficult to repeat what they heard in context from their peers. Here the teacher serves as a bridge to help the student pinpoint what they misunderstood. Furthermore, this activity should be practiced continuously to help the student perfect their active listening skills.
]]></string>
    <string name="offline_tool3_implementation"><![CDATA[<b>TOOL IMPLEMENTATION</b>
    <br><br>The setting for the implementation of this tool is within a multicultural classroom.  The teacher decides on the duration and resources needed for the activity.
<br><br>This tool has a three-step process.
<br><br><b>Step 1:	Selection of content:</b>
<br><br>The teacher describes a critical incident. “Critical incidents are tools for increasing our awareness and understanding of human attitudes, expectations, behaviours, and interactions” (Apedaile & Schill, 2008). The critical incident could range from not being time conscious, respect towards authority, being able to speak one\'s mind, etc. One way of identifying such incidents, as proposed by the developers of the tool (Fiedler, Mitchell, & Triandis, 1971), is to ask the students about intercultural occurrences or events that highlighted differences in attitude or behaviour towards members of other cultures. Such events could be pleasant, unpleasant or non-understandable occurrences. <br><br>This is an example of a critical incident as described by the developers of the tool. This example was posed by an American student studying in Thailand. <br><br>“The student indicated that he had had a number of appointments with Thai teachers, and that one thing that bothered him considerably was the lack of punctuality of the Thai professors. He asked some of his fellow Thai students if they were angry or disturbed over the tardiness of their teachers and they indicated that this happened rather frequently and that, yes, it disturbed them very much. The American thought about saying something to the teacher,  but decided against it when the Thai students said very strongly that although they were disturbed, they would never show their feelings to their professor” (source (Fiedler, Mitchell, & Triandis, 1971)).
<br><br><b>Step 2:	Use the content to simulate an encounter:</b> The next step is for the teacher to contextualise the critical incident in such a way that it provides the answer the student needs. The developers of the tool describe an example of such contextualisation.
<br><br>“One day a Thai administrator of middle academic rank kept two of his assistants waiting about an hour for an appointment.  The assistants, although very angry, did not show it while they waited. When the administrator walked in at last, he acted as if he were not late.  He made no apology or explanation.  After he was settled in his office, he called his assistants in and they all began working on the business for which the administrator had set the meeting” (source Fiedler, Mitchell, & Triandis, 1971).
<br><br>The contextualisation reveals the cultural response of locals to the critical incident. In order to simulate and contextualise critical incidents, the teacher ought to be conversant with the culture in question.  The teacher can educate his/herself by either reading or watching TV documentaries about that culture.
<br><br><b>Step 3:	Provide possible feedback and alternatives:</b>
<br><br>The third step involves the teacher leading the student in a reflection process. The reflection process is aimed at enabling students, foreign to the contextualised culture, to understand the cultural basis behind the critical incident. It also enables such students to compare their culture to the culture being contextualised. The reflection process also enables the students to correct their ethnocentric errors.
<br><br>The teacher provides a set of one correct, two plausible and one wrong answers to assist in the reflection process. An example used by the developers on the tool to deal with the American student’s dilemma is as follows:
<br><br>●	The Thai assistants were extremely skilful at concealing their true feelings (not entirely correct).
<br><br>●	The Thai administrator obviously was unaware of the fact that he was an hour late for the appointment (poor choice).
<br><br>●	In Thailand, subordinates are required to be polite to their superiors, no matter what happens, nor what their rank may be (correct).
<br><br>●	Clearly, since no one commented on it, the behaviour indicated nothing of any unusual significance to any of the Thais (wrong).

<br><br> The source of the example is (Fiedler, Mitchell, & Triandis, 1971)
<br><br>Students are given time to reflect and provide their answers. The teacher then provides the correct answer, while explaining why the other answers were either not totally correct or wrong.
]]></string>
    <string name="offline_tool4_implementation"><![CDATA[<b>TOOL IMPLEMENTATION</b>
    <br><br>The setting for this tool is inside and outside the multicultural classroom. In the multicultural classroom, a separate hour for the activity within a course should be set aside, if it is to be implemented within a course. The implementation of the tool outside the classroom could be in the form of an intercultural competence workshop or training session.
<br><br>The teacher decides the duration, scope and the resources needed for the activity, and should ensure that students are provided with writing materials for the exercise. The teacher should also provide a white board or a marker for illustrations. The teacher can also decide to be creative in their approach to the interaction.
<br><br><b>Step 1:	Identification of stereotypes.</b>
<br><br>The teacher randomly reads out a list consisting of ethnicity, last name, skin colour, cultural accent, disability, sexual preference, religion, nationality etc.
<br><br>The students lists what they feel and what comes to mind when they encounter anything read in the list.
<br><br><b>Step 2:	Looking for consistency.</b>
<br><br>The student reflects on their feelings. The reflection is aimed at finding out if their feelings for the listed items are consistent to a certain group of people or to just individuals. These questions guide the reflection process:
<br><br>●	Is my reaction consistent each time I encounter a member of a given group?
<br><br>●	Do my reactions occur before or after I have the opportunity to get to know the individual?
<br><br>●	The teacher then reveals to the student that the reaction is the basis for the negative reaction that occurs before they are acquainted with the individual.
<br><br><b>Step 3:	Developing anti-stereotype consciousness:</b>
<br><br>The teacher then instructs the student on how to become conscious of his/her stereotypes. The teacher reminds the student to:
<br><br>●	Judge an individual’s character, skills and personality not based on the group they belong to on the individual’s merit.
<br><br>●	Become aware that the automatic responses they identified are stereotypes, which are no accurate indicators of an individual’s character, skill or personality.
<br><br><b>Step 4:	Push stereotypes aside:</b>
<br><br>Finally, after they have identified their stereotypes, students need to consciously learn to ignore stereotypes and see individuals for who they are during encounters. To help the students in pushing their stereotypes aside, the teacher can heighten students’ awareness by using this quote from Howard Ross:
 <br><br>“Stereotyping is a habit. Just as it is learned through repetition, it can be unlearned through practice. Each time a thought you have identified as a stereotype appears, push it aside”.
]]></string>
    <string name="offline_tool5_implementation"><![CDATA[<b>TOOL IMPLEMENTATION</b>
    <br><br>The setting for the implementation of this tool is within a multicultural classroom. The teacher decides on the duration. In principle, this is not an activity that should take more than an hour. However, there could be circumstances due to class size where it might take longer to implement this tool. Hence, the teacher can use his or her discretion.
<br><br>To implement this tool, the teacher has to provide, the following:
<br><br>●	Flip charts
<br><br>●	Drawing materials (pens, board markers).
<br><br>●	Local charter of human rights and freedoms.
<br><br>Described below is the implementation process as extracted from Sarah Apedaile and Lenina Schill (2008):
	<br><br><b>Activity 1: Imagining prejudice</b>
<br><br><b>Step 1:</b>	Ask a student to draw an alien face on the board or flip chart. You can also draw the alien face yourself.
<br><br><b>Step 2:</b>	Invite students to describe what had been drawn on the board or flip chart.
<br><br><b>Step 3:</b>	Once all students have described what they see, the teacher then asks the following questions:
<br><br>●	“How do we know all this when we have never seen the character before?”
(Apedaile & Schill, 2008)
<br><br>●	or “How do we know all this when we have never met this character before?”
(Apedaile & Schill, 2008)
<br><br>●	Then ask, “What are we doing?” (Apedaile & Schill, 2008).

<br><br>It is likely that a student will identify their action as “prejudice”. If no student provides the correct answer, the teacher then identifies the action as prejudice.
<br><br><b>Step 4:</b>	The teacher then explains prejudice by exploring its Latin root ‘praejudicium’. Praejudicium means an opinion or judgement formed without due examination (Apedaile & Schill, 2008).

<br><br>The teacher then asks the participants:
<br><br>●	 “Has anyone ever thought or said something about you that was not true?” (Apedaile & Schill, 2008)
<br><br>●	“Have you ever thought or said something about someone else that wasn’t true, based on the person’s appearance/origin/sexual orientation?” (Apedaile & Schill, 2008).
	<br><br><b>Activity 2: Imagining Stereotyping</b>
<br><br><b>Step 1:</b>	The teacher then asks the participants to think about the character’s neighbourhood (or planet!); pretend that everyone in the neighbourhood is exactly the same and share their thoughts on what they think about the imaginary neighbourhood.
<br><br><b>Step 2:</b>	After students share their thoughts, the teacher then asks this question based on the thoughts shared by the students:
<br><br>“What are we doing when we say this (being one of the answers given by the student)?”

It is likely that a student will identify their action as “stereotyping”. If no student provides the correct answer, the teacher then identifies the action as stereotyping. The teacher explains what stereotyping is and proceeds to ask the participants about their experience with stereotyping. They could be the stereotyping they experienced or that which was directed at a group of people or individuals from a particular culture.
	<br><br><b>Activity 3: Imagining discrimination</b>
<br><br><b>	Step 1:</b> The teacher asks the participants to imagine that the character drawn on the flip chart or board comes into class and the students refuse access to the character as a result of their culture, race, or religion.
The teacher then asks: “What is that?”
It is likely that a student will identify their action as “discrimination”. If no student provides the correct answer, the teacher then identifies the action as discrimination. The teacher explains what discrimination means and proceeds to ask the participants about their experience with discrimination. They could be the stereotyping they experienced or that which was directed at a group of people or individuals from a particular culture.
	<br><br><b>Activity 4: Exchange of experience</b>
<br><br><b>Step 1:</b>	As a facilitator, share stories of prejudice, discrimination and stereotyping that you have experienced and how you felt. This is necessary to enable the students to open up to share their experience.
<br><br><b>Step 2:</b>	Ask the students to share their own stories of prejudice, discrimination and stereotyping and how they felt during the experience. This should not be a shaming experience for any student.
<br><br><b>Step 3:</b>	A good way of wrapping up the session is to read the local charter of rights and freedoms to the students. It is good practice to ensure they have a copy.

<br><br>It is important that the teacher is conversant with the level of language proficiency needed by their learners in order to gain the most benefit from this activity (Apedaile & Schill, 2008).

	<br><br>REFERENCES
	<br>For more information on this tool, visit: https://www.norquest.ca/NorquestCollege/media/pdf/centres/intercultural/CriticalIncidentsBooklet.pdf
]]></string>
    <string name="offline_tool6_implementation"><![CDATA[<b>TOOL IMPLEMENTATION</b>
    <br><br>The setting for the implementation of this tool is a multicultural classroom and the students should be clustered in multicultural groups for the activity. The teacher decides the duration and the resources needed for the activity. This demands creativity and innovation on the part of the teacher.
<br><br>●	All the students’ individual assignments within a group are related to each other in such a way that every student receives some but not all the pieces of the overall group assignment.
<br><br>●	Individual students have to master their own assignments and then teach them to the other members of the group – thus, each individual spends a part of their time taking on the role of an expert and exercising their communication skills. Each student must listen to all the other students in their group, ask appropriate questions, and master all the material – thus, the assignment requires both individual work and teamwork. The individual or teamwork could be via individual or joint search on the internet on the topic assigned to the student. Teamwork could be via group dialogue with the student, whose culture they are learning about.
<br><br>●	The overall group assignment is to synthesise all the individual contributions in order to construct a complete picture – the assignment therefore culminates in a whole group problem-solving task.
<br><br>●	The structure of the jigsaw activity means that every group member becomes equally important. Because students have to rely on each other in order to do well, their competitive attitudes are reduced, and their cooperative attitudes are enhanced – the group can only succeed if every student succeeds.
]]></string>
    <string name="offline_tool7_implementation"><![CDATA[<b>TOOL IMPLEMENTATION</b>
    <br><br>All students - local and foreigners - were asked to read the book “Feeling Italian” (Di Mauro & Gehrke, 2018) within the first course week, where the teacher tackles issues such as: culture, cultural identity, global identity, human mobility, becoming a global and sustainable manager. Consequently, to reflect on their learnings by answering - individually and in written form - a list of 10 questions. The overall number of words that constitute their answers is limited to 5000 characters-including spaces.
<br><br><b>Questions:</b>
<br><br>●	By reading the ‘Feeling Italian’ book, did you learn anything new or surprising about the Italians today?
<br><br>●	What aspect(s) of the book make you particularly reflect on your identity and/or country of origin?
<br><br>●	Think of the groups you feel you belong to. How are they important in defining the person you are today?
<br><br>●	How and why did your membership in these groups contribute to you being the person you are today?
<br><br>●	Think of the culture(s) you feel you have a sense of belonging to. What are the traditional elements of that culture/s you feel attached to?
<br><br>●	Think of the culture(s) to which you feel you belong. What are the innovative or diverse elements you bring to them, if any?
<br><br>●	How do these groups’ membership contribute to developing your professional identity?
<br><br>●	Have you ever thought about yourself as a citizen of the world? How did the ‘Feeling Italian’ book affect your view of yourself as a global citizen?
<br><br>●	Are there any social or global challenges that are relevant to you or that you feel particularly committed to?
<br><br>●	As a future global citizen, is there anything you think you could do to contribute to solving these challenges?
	<br><br><b>REFERENCES</b>
<br>For more information, read: Self-Reflection Assignment based on ‘Feeling Italian’ by Prof. Maura Di Mauro – Intercultural Management, Università Cattolica del Sacro Cuore, Piacenza: https://centerforinterculturaldialogue.files.wordpress.com/2021/02/icd-exercise-2-di-mauro.pdf]]></string>
    <string name="offline_tool8_implementation"><![CDATA[<b>TOOL IMPLEMENTATION</b>
    <br><br>●	The teacher decides on the topic of interest and the methodology.
<br><br>●	Students are divided into small groups, preferably a mix of foreign and local students.
<br><br>●	Students may adopt either joint desk-based research or individual interviews to research the topic provided by the teacher.
<br><br>●	Students then present either video or PowerPoint presentations of their findings and new discoveries about the culture investigated.  The presentation is made to other groups of students, who also share what they learn from their own research.
<br><br>●	The students are then asked to write a report on their experience.]]></string>
    <string name="offline_tool9_implementation"><![CDATA[<b>TOOL IMPLEMENTATION</b>
    <br><br>The setting for the implementation of this tool is within a multicultural classroom. The teacher determines the duration of the activity. However, 45 minutes is ideal. The resources needed for the activity includes a book consisting of very short stories about a particular culture or nationality. The book should be available for all students in the class.
<br><br>The instructions for the activities are as follows:
<br><br><b>Step 1:</b>	The students are placed in pairs and given the following instructions:
<br><br>●	You will be given one small book to read together. You should complete the book in three minutes. Only start reading when I say so.
<br><br>●	Read the book silently and do not communicate with your partner for the duration of the three minutes. Do go through every page.
<br><br>●	When you are done reading the book, close it and wait for your partner to complete theirs as well.
<br><br><b>Step 2:</b>	Allow the students to read the book in pairs. (Two students can share one book!). Give them 3 minutes.
<br><br><b>Step 3:</b>	After three minutes, you do give the chance for the students who have not finished the book to do so.
<br><br><b>Step 4:</b>	When all students are done reading the book, ask the students to share their thoughts in pairs for about 5 minutes.
<br><br><b>Step 5:</b>	Ask the pairs to select a word that best describes the book and to share that word with the big group.
<br><br><b>Step 6:</b>	Ask the pairs to select one picture in the book that they both like.
<br><br><b>Step 7:</b>	Ask them to reveal to each other what they “see, hear, smell, taste and feel” (“what they feel with their body/hands but also in their hearts”).
<br><br><b>Step 8:</b>	Use the phrase: “Once upon a time…” and construct a story with the help of the sentences inspired in the chosen picture selected in stage 6.
<br><br><b>Step 9:</b>	Now instruct each pair of students to sit together with another pair and to narrate to each other the stories you have constructed. Talk about new words.
<br><br><b>Step 10:</b>	Discuss the following questions in the new groups of four:
<br><br>●	“Are you familiar with these places?”
<br><br>●	“Do they remind you of something? (Places you have visited, people you have met, feelings that you have felt?)”
<br><br><b>Step 11:</b>	Provide each student with laminated pages from the book. The students should not show their page to anyone else.
<br><br><b>Step 12:</b>	Ask them to mingle in the room and ask each other this question:
<br><br>●	“What do you see in your picture?”
<br><br>Based on the information given they will place themselves in the right order so when everybody reveals their picture, every page comes in the right order. “If there are less participants than pages of the book, just use a part of the book, maybe the beginning, the end or a part in the middle somewhere”.
<br><br>“The students can continue working with the book:
<br><br>● drama/theatre and make up/improvise short dialogues or happenings inspired by the pictures in the book.
<br><br>● write dialogues, stories inspired by the pictures in the book
<br><br>● add music to the pictures
<br><br>● talk about their own experiences from life inspired by the pictures in the book.
<br><br>Think about/discuss: If you think about your own life right now and “zoom in”, what will you find? And what if you “zoom out”?”
	<br><br>REFERENCES
The tool is extracted from Bupnet.eu. This is the source of all direct quotes.
]]></string>
    <string name="offline_tool10_implementation"><![CDATA[<b>TOOL IMPLEMENTATION</b>
    <br><br>See tool description]]></string>
    <string name="online_tool1_implementation"><![CDATA[<b>TOOL IMPLEMENTATION</b><br><br><b>Tool:</b> How to be a_________?, based on “Feeling Italian” by Di Mauro & Gherke (2020)
<br><br> <b>Goal, objective:</b> To increase the awareness of the student of the features of the culture that they are in and to open their eyes to different perspectives on how others see the culture.
<br><br><b>Actors: </b> Student groups instructed by teachers.
<br><br><b>Target Group, volume: </b> The main task can be carried out independently by the group once the instructions are given, and thus there is no limitation to the number of participants.
<br><br><b>Time frame:</b>A single event. Can include follow-up reflections and thus extend over a longer time. Time allocation needed for each group is ~15 minutes of individual preparation and ~1 hour of discussion by the group. Reflections and follow-ups, if carried out, increase the usage of time accordingly.
<br><br><b>Technological requirements:  Hardware: </b>Stable internet connection; a device to use a group-call application, microphone and preferably a camera.
<br><b>Software:</b> a working group-call application that enables screen-sharing (e.g. Teams,Zoom etc.).
<br><br><b>Neighbourness competence outcome: </b>Increasing awareness of self as well as of the thinking of others.
<br><br><b>Teacher’s approach: </b> Prepare to help students to recognize cultural stereotypes, and countries’ internal diversities. Be ready to reflect the verbal and nonverbal elements from the classroom conversations and guide the conversation appropriately from an ethnocentric vs. ethnorelative perspective.]]></string>

    <string name="online_tool2_implementation"><![CDATA[<b>TOOL IMPLEMENTATION</b>
<br><br><b>Tool:</b> Collaborative case analysis with Flinga
<br><br><b>Goal, objective:</b> To collaboratively explore real-life cases.
<br><br><b>Actors:</b> Facilitator; students from different cultures
<br><br><b>Target Group, volume:</b> Around 10-50 students
<br><br><b>Time frame:</b> 90-120 minutes
<br><br><b>Technological requirements: Hardware:</b> A stable internet connection; a device to use an online group chat along with a microphone. Camera is preferred
<b>Software:</b> Online group chat application (e.g. Teams or Zoom); A web-browser to access Flinga (https://flinga.fi/)</b>
<br><br><b>Neighbourness competence outcome:</b> Increase students’ awareness of how other individuals may see different situations. Gaining experience in collaboration with peers.</b>
<br><br><b>Teacher’s approach:</b> Become fluent with the chosen online platform (e.g. Flinga). Prepare to guide students’ thoughts into cultural issues. Be to recognize where students from different cultures could contribute by sharing their thoughts on different issues.</b>

]]>

    </string>
    <string name="online_tool3_implementation"><![CDATA[<b>TOOL IMPLEMENTATION</b>
<br><br><b>Tool:</b> Sensitising with Web Questionnaires
<br><br><b>Goal, objective:</b> To sensitise students to cultural matters before the course’s main exercises.
<br><br><b>Actors:</b> Students.
<br><br><b>Target Group, volume:</b> Students.
<br><br><b>Time frame:</b> Approximately 15-30 minutes
<br><br><b>Technological requirements: Hardware:</b> Internet access
<br><b>Software:</b> web-browser; suitable web-questionnaire. e.g. https://implicit.harvard.edu/implicit/takeatest.html.
<br><br><b>Neighbourness competence outcome: </b> Increase students’ awareness of cultural issues.
<br><br><b>Teacher’s approach:</b> Become fluent with the chosen online platform (e.g. Flinga). Prepare to guide students’ thoughts into cultural issues. Be to recognize where students from different cultures could contribute by sharing their thoughts on different issues.</b>]]></string>
    <string name="online_tool4_implementation"><![CDATA[<b>TOOL IMPLEMENTATION</b>
    <br><br><b>TOOL 4.1: Neighborness Storytelling Workshop - Storytelling Gamified</b>
<br><br><b>Tool:</b> Neighborness Storytelling Workshop – Storytelling  Gamified
<br><br><b>Goal, objective:</b> To give the participants a chance to experiment with the process of storytelling, to observe and reflect on the way each member of their group handles the story.
<br><br><b>Actors:</b> Teams of 4 students who ideally come from different backgrounds.
The number of teams is variable, but more than 4 teams per facilitator could become unwieldy. 1 facilitator / moderator
<br><br><b>Target Group, volume:</b> Students of different cultures interested in storytelling, particularly filmic and theatrical.
<br><br><b>Time frame:</b> The shortest version possible would take around 4 hours.
<br><br><b>Technological requirements: Hardware:</b> A stable internet connection on a computer with a microphone and a camera. Any modern laptop would do.
<br><b>Software:</b> A web-browser, an app to voice/video-chat, an online whiteboard and Fiascomputer website (https://fiasco.tabletopsoftware.net/)
<br><br><b>Neighbourness competence outcome: </b> Advancing students’ skills for collaboration through exercises. Increasing students’ awareness regarding how others see the world.
<br><br><b>Teacher’s approach:</b> Become familiar with the Fiasco storytelling game. Be prepared to help students to reflect on their experiences.

<br><br><br><b>TOOL 4.2: Neighborness Storytelling Workshop - A Letter From Across The Channel </b>

<br><br><b>Tool:</b>Transnational Storytelling
<br><br><b>Goal, objective:</b>Connect students from two universities from different countries through a collaborative storytelling speed-run
<br><br><b>Actors:</b>Teams of Students (2-4 per institution per group)
<br>One professor/lecturer per institution, ideally with one being a specialist in transnational storytelling
<br><br><b>Target Group, volume:</b>Students of different cultures interested in storytelling, particularly filmic and theatrical.
<br><br><b>Time frame:</b>One week (not necessarily full-time)
<br><br><b>Technological requirements:</b>
<br>Hardware:</b> A stable internet connection on a computer with a microphone and a camera. Any modern laptop would do.
<br><br>Equipment needed for the production of the artform picked by the coordinators. E.g. cameras and microphones for film, studios for podcasts, etc.
<br><br><b>Software:</b> A web-browser, an app to voice/video-chat, a team coordination tool like Slack.
<br><br><b>Neighbourness competence outcome:</b> Advancing students’ skills for collaboration through exercises. Increasing students’ awareness regarding how others see the world.
<br><br><b>Teacher’s approach:</b>Become familiar with transnational storytelling. Be prepared to help students to reflect on their experiences.
]]></string>
    <string name="online_tool5_implementation"><![CDATA[<b>TOOL IMPLEMENTATION</b>
<br><br><b>Tool:</b> MIPPS (Method of Intercultural Project Presentation and Socialising)
<br><br><b>Goal, objective:</b> Organising a virtual online speed dating event where students from all around the world can virtually meet each other.
<br><br><b>Actors:</b> Students of different cultures (be it national, professional, social or otherwise) are interested in networking and new ideas.
<br><br><b>Target Group, volume:</b> Participants (up to 100 people per room); moderator (recommended but not necessary); map editor (in preparation, not while the event)
<br><br><b>Time frame:</b> Depends on the amount of participants. The ultimate network tool is a speed dating event. People randomly pick a seat and after fifteen minutes the moderator asks all participants to change their seat. There are as many rounds as tables.
<br><br><b>Technological requirements: Hardware:</b> A stable internet connection on a computer with a microphone and a camera. Any modern laptop would do (as of April 2021, Gather.town doesn’t work via a mobile device). <b>Software:</b> A web-browser, (but not Safari), and the link to the gather.town room
  <br><br><b>Neighbourness competence outcome: </b> Advancement in student’s neighbourness skills through exercising intercultural communication
<br><br><b>Teacher’s approach/teaching notes:</b> Become fluent with Gather.town. Be prepared to inspire students to be creative. </b>]]></string>
    <string name="online_tool6_implementation"><![CDATA[<b>TOOL IMPLEMENTATION</b>
<br><br><b>Tool:</b> Audience Exploration
<br><br><b>Goal, objective:</b> Initiating a discussion among the students about how to negotiate their story with an anticipated audience and in that way make them question their own stereotypical and/or not sufficiently complex assumptions about those they speak to.
<br><br><b>Actors:</b> Teams of 4 students who ideally come from different backgrounds. The number of teams is variable, but more than 4 teams per facilitator could become unwieldy. ‘
<br>1 facilitator / moderator

<br><br><b>Target Group, volume:</b> A diverse group of students in terms of age, class, race and gender, particularly from creative & artistic backgrounds.
<br><br><b>Time frame:</b> Around 4 hours.
<br><br><b>Technological requirements: Hardware:</b> Stable internet connection; a device with microphone and webcam
<br><b>Software:</b> Web-browser (which runs MIRO) / zoom-app (with 4 breakout rooms)
  <br><br><b>Neighbourness competence outcome: </b> Increasing in understanding others perspectives
<br><br><b>Teacher’s approach/teaching notes: </b> Become fluent with the MIRO. Be prepared to help the groups in completing the exercise. Be ready to inspire reflection regarding cultural matters the exercises may have brought to surface.]]></string>
    <string name="online_tools_description_1"><![CDATA[The tool How to be a_________? is one of the simpler neighbourness learning online tools. The tool is based on the book “Feeling Italian” written by Di Mauro and Gherke (2020). The tool is useful in many situations as it does not take much more than an hour to complete. A natural situation would be to use it at the beginning of a course so that the students are able to become more familiar with each other before diving into group exercises. This tool is about inspiring the students to consider their own and other’s culture. In particular, the tool guides the students to identify and reflect the stereotypes associated with different cultures. Students are encouraged to grasp the surface of different cultures, become more aware of the cultural stereotypes, consider the extent and limits of the simplified definitions that stereotypes impose about different cultures, and become familiar with other students. <br><br>Students should first be instructed in the use of the tool. The tasks, however, are not complicated so the introduction should not take an excessive amount of time. Students should first be asked to select a picture that to them represents being a member of a particular culture. Approximately 15 minutes should be enough for each student to find a picture and prepare a few words about it. The picture can, for instance, convey what it means to be a Finnish person. Stereotypically such a picture could be a picture from nature or of a sauna, as those are often associated with Finland. The picture may be selected from the student\'s own pictures or from the internet. Then, in a group meeting via an online platform such as Teams or Zoom, students will go through the pictures they have selected. The online platform should have functionalities for sharing/showing the pictures, and for verbally presenting and discussing in a group. Everyone will show the chosen pictures and give a short explanation of why they have chosen those pictures and whether they had other options. Presentations may be only a couple of minutes long or longer. After everyone has gone through their pictures the group will discuss what similarities and differences they found in the pictures and whether any stereotypes could be found. The groups should be instructed to reserve around 30–45 minutes for this discussion. <br><br>The tool could also be used offline. Instructions could be given in advance so the students would have time to find the pictures, but the discussion part could be held in a classroom. The impact of the tool may be different with students physically present and the conversation may be better. <br><br>The goal of the tool is to increase the awareness of students of both their own culture and of other cultures, and to open their eyes to different perspectives. By choosing a picture that represents a student\'s own culture, the aim is to make the students consider their own cultures. Discussing these choices in the group will inspire students to think about other cultures or how other students see their culture. Ultimately, the goal is to make the students think about their own culture from other perspectives. <br><br>The teacher may guide the discussions to focus on reflecting the stereotypes. The teacher could inspire the discussion with questions such as ‘what does it mean to feel like a citizen of a country? What are the behaviours, places, situations, activities or symbols that evoke citizenship? What are the elements of continuity with the past that allow the person to perceive or be perceived as the citizen of a country?’ In this way the discussion could be aligned to focus on reflection rather than merely mentioning the most obvious stereotypes. If the same pictures are often chosen the teacher may suggest that the students discuss the reason why.]]></string>
    <string name="online_tools_description_2"><![CDATA[This tool is simple to implement. The most obvious use scenario for the Collaborative Case Analysis with Flinga is to use it to support case-based teaching. In disciplines such as information technology or business, teaching often combines theoretical lectures and applying them to real-life cases. Analyzing the cases together brings multiple different perspectives together as the students analyze the case from their respective cultural frames. However, in physical face-to-face meetings, some perspectives may easily be left in the shadows as the possibilities for contribution are limited. In addition, voicing an opinion verbally requires courage and may be difficult for students from a culture where students are not used to being verbally active during lectures. Nevertheless, contributions from all students are crucial in creating a multicultural teaching environment that leverages the different perspectives embedded into the group of students. Flinga, a collaborative whiteboard accessed via a web browser whereby participants can contribute by adding textboxes to the online whiteboard. The textboxes can be seen by all participants. In this way, the tool offers a relatively simple and safe space for collaborative work for students from different cultures. Students may thus contribute to case exploration from their own perspective and then see other students’ inputs and learn about their perceptions while still focusing on the course’s main topic. <br><br>The teacher should first pick the case(s) to be analysed. The decision could be prioritised based on the course’s main topic. However, teachers are encouraged to choose cases that are also culturally challenging so that the different perspectives on cultural issues can be activated. The teacher should be familiar with the Flinga teaching environment. Flinga is relatively simple to learn and many tutorial videos can be found on the internet. Then the teacher should set up a Flinga whiteboard in advance so that this won\'t take up time during the actual activities. The teacher should share the link to the Flinga room for students and make sure that the students also make themselves familiar with Flinga’s basic functionalities. Naturally, the teacher should also organise an online group meeting through Teams or Zoom (or similar) and make sure that the students can access the meeting. <br><br>The teacher can organise the analysable case as it best serves the course. However, a suggested option is to make the students study the case individually beforehand and consider their thoughts. This could mean reading a case description and preparing simple notes. This preparation could also be done in groups, but making the students first consider the case individually may encourage them to consider the case from an culturally-framed individual perspective. <br><br>The teacher should initially gather the students into an online group meeting. Here, the teacher briefly introduces the case and instructs the students. The teacher may have previously added categories, themes, or topics into the Flinga whiteboard to organise students’ inputs. Then the teacher allows the students time to contribute to the Flinga whiteboard. This could be for instance 15 – 30 minutes. In this stage, the students add their ideas about the case as textboxes into the Flinga whiteboard. <br><br>Once individual contributions to the whiteboard have ended, the inputs are discussed together. This may be organised in many ways, but one way is that the teacher identifies the most interesting inputs first. The teacher could ask the corresponding student to verbally reflect the input. The teacher is encouraged to not actively contribute too much to the discussion, but instead rather facilitate it - the students provide the content. During this stage, connections between the inputs/textbox can be drawn to illustrate their relationships. This may be inspired by the teacher or, better yet, by the students. The teacher may also guide the students in considering cultural influences. This could mean that first, the teacher suggests that some differences in inputs may result from cultural issues, and second, that findings from the case under analysis may include cultural influences. In the latter case, the teacher may for instance mention that the organisational issues studied in the case could have cultural factors embedded. This could result in insightful discussion as students from different cultures provide their view. <br><br>The tool ends with a brief reflective discussion where the main points are summarised. It may be easier if the teacher takes the lead in this stage. However, the students are expected to contribute.]]></string>
    <string name="online_tools_description_3"><![CDATA[This tool is also easy to implement and does not require much from the learning environment. Sensitising with Web Questionnaires is useful especially in the early stages of a course when students are getting into the mindset of the selected approach. The tool assumes that during the first moments of the course, for instance during the first introductory lectures, students generally have an open mindset as they try to absorb what the course is essentially about. The idea is to leverage this stage by sensitising students to be aware not only of the course\'s main topics but also of cultural matters that they may face in the course content and during collaboration with other students. Thus, the tool may be used before the course’s main group project. The tool requires only that students have internet access and a suitable web questionnaire
        <br><br>The tool can be implemented by simply asking the students to fill out a web questionnaire. In this way the students may test their awareness of cultural issues, learn more about these issues and, more importantly, become sensitised to cultural matters. Teachers may search for suitable web questionnaires/exercises on their own. For instance, the website Learning for Justice offers questionnaires to test cultural biases and stereotypes (https://implicit.harvard.edu/implicit/selectatest.html). Additionally, the teacher may try to further activate the students’ thinking with other material such as videos (e.g. The Importance of Cultural Humility: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cVmOXVIF8wc), movies, articles, etc. before filling out the questionnaires.
        <br><br>Students should complete the questionnaires/exercises individually so that they process the issues themselves. However, teachers may complement this with some reflection exercises. This could be for instance a group discussion where students briefly share their thoughts, such as lessons learnt, surprises, etc. with other students. Alternatively, or additionally, students may also be asked to write a short self-reflective essay about their experiences with the questionnaire. An online forum may be utilised where each student may share their thoughts and comment on those of other students.]]></string>
     <string name="online_tools_description_5"><![CDATA[Online platforms for virtual meetings, such as Gather.town, are great replacements for meetups and events that would naturally have been offline but under the circumstances (such as the Covid-19 pandemic) must be organised remotely. Such circumstances have provided the opportunity to design events to be more international and intercultural. This makes Gather.town a very useful platform for intercultural events. It can be used for networking or “speed dating” events, for pitching, for group finding and group work. These platforms can and should also be used in the development of intercultural competences. The tool MIPPS: Method of Intercultural Project Presentation and Socialising leverages the possibilities of the online virtual meeting platform Gather.town to introduce students to an engaging learning experience <br><br>The idea of this tool is relatively simple and offers many possibilities. Teachers should be acquainted with the Gather.town platform and should ideally have participated in a few events themselves. The better they understand the mechanics and possibilities, the better they will be able to adapt it to their context. In preparation for each event a room has to be set up. One may use a preset that suits the numbers of participants and the event. It is also possible to design one from scratch via the online map editor on Gather.town. The map editor is relatively simple to use and the Gather.town website provides many tutorials. The design can be very individual. One can use the layout of an actual building (like university e.g.) or add some Easter eggs for fun. <br><br>The ultimate online tool is a speed dating event. Therefore it requires a room with small tables and two to four chairs each. If one has 40 students participating,then ten to thirteen tables are needed. In this tool the students would randomly pick a seat, and after fifteen minutes the teacher acting as a moderator asks all students to change their seats. The student on the top chair would walk to the table above, the student on the bottom chair to the table below and so on, the student on the left chair to the table on the left and the student on the right chair stays. There are as many rounds as tables, so that everybody in the event can visit a new table with up to three new people every round.]]></string>
    <string name="tool_description">Tool Description:</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>


</resources>