<resources>
    <string name="app_name">WeLearn</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="tips">Tips</string>
    <string name="please_check_device_internet_connection">Please check device internet connection</string>
    <string name="str_about">WeLearn is a project that aims to find ways for informing teachers and students in higher education to support neighbourness in their multicultural learning environments. We study neighbourness practices and create instructions for educators and students on how to embrace those practices to make the learning environments, digital and physical, better for all. The WeLearn project consortium consists of six European partners. Tampere University, Riga Technical University, Film University Babelsber, Aalborg University, Catholic University of Sacred Heart and Suleyman Demirel University. The WeLearn project is lead by Tampere University, while Riga Technical University is in charge of the technical development of the WeLearn mobile application. \n \nThe content of this application represents the views of the author only and is his/her sole responsibility. The European Commission and the Agency do not accept any responsibility for use that may be made of the information it contains.</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="finish">Finish</string>
    <string name="online">Online</string>
    <string name="offline" >Offline</string>
    <string name="both">Both</string>
    <string name="dismiss">Dismiss</string>
    <string name="tips_online">Tips: Online</string>
    <string name="tips_offline">Tips: Offline</string>
    <string name="tips_online_offline">Tips: Online / Offline</string>
    <string name="test_result">Test Result</string>
    <string name="selection_of_content_n_n_the_teacher_describes_a_critical_incident_critical_incidents_are_tools_for_increasing_our_awareness_and_understanding_of_human_attitudes_expectations_behaviours_and_interactions_apedaile_schill_2008_the_critical_incident_could_range_from_not_being_time_conscious_respect_towards_authority_being_able_to_speak_one_s_mind_etc_one_way_of_identifying_such_incidents_as_proposed_by_the_developers_of_the_tool_fiedler_mitchell_triandis_1971_is_to_ask_the_students_about_intercultural_occurrences_or_events_that_highlighted_differences_in_attitude_or_behaviour_towards_members_of_other_cultures_such_events_could_be_pleasant_unpleasant_or_non_understandable_occurrences_this_is_an_example_of_a_critical_incident_as_described_by_the_developers_of_the_tool_this_example_was_posed_by_an_american_student_studying_in_thailand_the_student_indicated_that_he_had_had_a_number_of_appointments_with_thai_teachers_and_that_one_thing_that_bothered_him_considerably_was_the_lack_of_punctuality_of_the_thai_professors_he_asked_some_of_his_fellow_thai_students_if_they_were_angry_or_disturbed_over_the_tardiness_of_their_teachers_and_they_indicated_that_this_happened_rather_frequently_and_that_yes_it_disturbed_them_very_much_the_american_thought_about_saying_something_to_the_teacher_but_decided_against_it_when_the_thai_students_said_very_strongly_that_although_they_were_disturbed_they_would_never_show_their_feelings_to_their_professor_fiedler_mitchell_triandis_1971_n_n_use_the_content_to_simulate_an_encounter_n_n_the_next_step_is_for_the_teacher_to_contextualize_the_critical_incident_in_such_a_way_that_it_provides_the_answer_the_student_needs_the_developers_of_the_tool_describe_an_example_of_such_contextualization_one_day_a_thai_administrator_of_middle_academic_rank_kept_two_of_his_assistants_waiting_about_an_hour_for_an_appointment_the_assistants_although_very_angry_did_not_show_it_while_they_waited_when_the_administrator_walked_in_at_last_he_acted_as_if_he_were_not_late_he_made_no_apology_or_explanation_after_he_was_settled_in_his_office_he_called_his_assistants_in_and_they_all_began_working_on_the_business_for_which_the_administrator_had_set_the_meeting_source_fiedler_mitchell_triandis_1971_the_contextualization_reveals_the_cultural_response_of_locals_to_the_critical_incident_inorder_to_simulate_and_contextualize_critical_incidents_the_teacher_ought_to_be_conversant_with_the_culture_in_question_the_teacher_can_educate_his_herself_by_either_reading_or_watching_tv_documentaries_about_that_culture_n_n_provide_possible_feedback_and_alternatives_n_n_the_third_step_involves_the_teacher_leading_the_student_in_a_reflection_process_the_reflection_process_is_aimed_at_enabling_students_foreign_to_the_contextualized_culture_to_understand_the_cultural_basis_behind_the_critical_incident_it_also_enables_such_students_to_compare_their_culture_to_the_culture_being_contextualized_the_reflection_process_also_enables_the_students_to_correct_their_ethnocentric_errors_the_teacher_provides_a_set_of_one_correct_two_plausible_and_one_wrong_answers_to_assist_in_the_reflection_process_an_example_used_by_the_developers_on_the_tool_to_deal_with_the_american_student_s_dilemma_is_as_follows_n_n_o_the_thai_assistants_were_extremely_skillful_at_concealing_their_true_feelings_not_entirely_correct_n_n_o_the_thai_administrator_obviously_was_unaware_of_the_fact_that_he_was_an_hour_late_for_the_appointment_poor_choice_n_n_o_in_thailand_subordinates_are_required_to_be_polite_to_their_superiors_no_matter_what_happens_nor_what_their_rank_may_be_correct_n_n_o_clearly_since_no_one_commented_on_it_the_behavior_indicated_nothing_of_any_unusual_significance_to_any_of_the_thais_wrong_n_n_the_source_of_the_example_is_fiedler_mitchell_triandis_1971_students_are_given_time_to_reflect_and_provide_their_answers_the_teacher_then_provides_the_correct_answer_while_explaining_why_the_other_answers_were_either_not_totally_correct_or_wrong"><![CDATA[● Selection of content: \n \n The teacher describes a critical incident. “Critical incidents are tools for increasing our awareness and understanding of human attitudes, expectations, behaviours, and interactions” (Apedaile & Schill, 2008). The critical incident could range from not being time conscious, respect towards authority, being able to speak one\'s mind, etc. One way of identifying such incidents, as proposed by the developers of the tool (Fiedler, Mitchell, & Triandis, 1971), is to ask the students about intercultural occurrences or events that highlighted differences in attitude or behaviour towards members of other cultures. Such events could be pleasant, unpleasant or non-understandable occurrences. This is an example of a critical incident as described by the developers of the tool. This example was posed by an American student studying in Thailand. “The student indicated that he had had a number of appointments with Thai teachers, and that one thing that bothered him considerably was the lack of punctuality of the Thai professors. He asked some of his fellow Thai students if they were angry or disturbed over the tardiness of their teachers and they indicated that this happened rather frequently and that, yes, it disturbed them very much. The American thought about saying something to the teacher, but decided against it when the Thai students said very strongly that although they were disturbed they would never show their feelings to their professor”( (Fiedler, Mitchell, & Triandis, 1971)). \n \n ● Use the content to simulate an encounter: \n \n The next step is for the teacher to contextualize the critical incident in such a way that it provides the answer the student needs. The developers of the tool describe an example of such contextualization. “One day a Thai administrator of middle academic rank kept two of his assistants waiting about an hour for an appointment. The assistants, although very angry, did not show it while they waited. When the administrator walked in at last, he acted as if he were not late. He made no apology or explanation. After he was settled in his office, he called his assistants in and they all began working on the business for which the administrator had set the meeting” (source (Fiedler, Mitchell, & Triandis, 1971)). The contextualization reveals the cultural response of locals to the critical incident. Inorder to simulate and contextualize critical incidents, the teacher ought to be conversant with the culture in question. The teacher can educate his/herself by either reading or watching TV documentaries about that culture. \n \n ● Provide possible feedback and alternatives: \n \n The third step involves the teacher leading the student in a reflection process. The reflection process is aimed at enabling students, foreign to the contextualized culture, to understand the cultural basis behind the critical incident. It also enables such students to compare their culture to the culture being contextualized. The reflection process also enables the students to correct their ethnocentric errors. The teacher provides a set of one correct, two plausible and one wrong answers to assist in the reflection process. An example used by the developers on the tool to deal with the American student’s dilemma is as follows: \n \n o The Thai assistants were extremely skillful at concealing their true feelings. (not entirely correct). \n \n o The Thai administrator obviously was unaware of the fact that he was an hour late for the appointment (poor choice) \n \n o In Thailand, subordinates are required to be polite to their superiors, no matter what happens, nor what their rank may be. (correct) \n \n o Clearly, since no one commented on it, the behavior indicated nothing of any unusual significance to any of the Thais (wrong) \n \n The source of the example is (Fiedler, Mitchell, & Triandis, 1971) Students are given time to reflect and provide their answers. The teacher then provides the correct answer, while explaining why the other answers were either not totally correct or wrong.]]></string>
    <string name="tool_implementation_n_n_activity_1_preparation_process_n_n_step_1_the_teacher_inscribes_the_quote_cards_with_non_verbal_behavior_that_often_results_in_misunderstanding_the_teacher_can_take_inspiration_for_the_non_verbal_behaviours_from_critical_incidents_the_teacher_can_then_inscribe_these_critical_incidents_in_the_quotecards_n_n_step_2_the_quote_cards_should_consist_of_non_verbal_behaviours_from_the_different_cultures_represented_in_that_multicultural_classroom_n_n_step_3_the_teacher_then_divides_the_students_into_small_groups_with_each_grouprepresenting_students_from_different_cultures_n_n_step_4_the_teacher_introduces_the_students_to_the_concept_of_the_iceberg_metaphor_apa_2021_n_n_activity_2_knowledge_acquisition_process_n_n_step_1_the_teacher_shares_the_quote_cards_to_the_individual_small_groups_n_n_step_2_the_students_are_instructed_to_read_the_cards_and_sort_them_into_categories_of_their_choosing_n_n_step_3_once_sorted_each_group_must_then_name_the_categories_as_either_acceptable_behaviour_or_non_acceptable_behaviour_explain_the_reasoning_behind_their_choice_n_n_the_teacher_points_out_how_the_categories_fit_within_the_iceberg_in_the_explanation_the_teacher_explains_how_nob_verbal_behavior_attitude_is_hidden_underneath_the_iceberg_and_the_verbal_behavior_is_above_the_iceberg_and_why_it_is_hidden_n_n_activity_2_helps_the_students_to_become_sensitive_and_aware_of_acceptable_and_nonacceptable_non_verbal_behaviours_from_different_cultural_perspectives_a_possible_outcome_is_that_some_students_might_develop_empathy_towards_their_colleagues_from_other_cultures_this_opens_up_the_possibility_for_behavior_modification_apedaile_schill_2008_n_n_activity_3_behaviour_modification_process_students_are_provided_with_conscious_behavior_modification_tips_by_the_teacher_such_tips_include_n_n_conscious_relay_of_non_verbal_communication_apedaile_and_schill_2008_suggest_telling_the_student_thus_be_aware_of_your_own_non_verbal_communication_apedaile_schill_2008_this_enables_the_student_to_understand_that_others_may_neither_understand_nor_be_aware_of_the_non_verbal_behaviour_he_or_she_exhibits_hence_polite_verbal_communication_might_serve_a_better_purpose_than_non_verbal_communication_that_others_do_not_understand_n_n_selective_judgement_of_non_verbal_communication_apedaile_and_schill_2008_suggest_telling_the_student_thus_be_aware_of_others_behaviours_and_how_these_affect_you_unexpected_and_unfamiliar_non_verbal_behaviours_can_cause_strong_responses_at_an_emotional_level_resist_the_temptation_to_make_hasty_judgmental_evaluations_apedaile_schill_2008_this_helps_the_student_not_to_be_alert_in_always_trying_to_interpret_allnon_verbal_communications_n_n_conscious_behaviour_modification_apedaile_and_schill_2008_suggest_telling_the_student_thus_try_to_match_your_behaviour_to_those_of_the_culture_you_are_interacting_with_this_involves_the_integration_of_the_foreign_student_to_the_culture_of_the_host_country_the_teacher_should_also_inform_the_student_thus_changing_how_you_behave_and_how_you_understand_others_non_verbal_communication_is_the_key_to_successful_non_verbal_communication_across_cultures_apedaile_schill_2008_n_n_do_note_that_the_onus_for_behaviour_modification_is_on_the_student_the_teacher_only_raises_awareness"><![CDATA[TOOL IMPLEMENTATION \n \n Activity 1: Preparation process \n \n ● Step 1: The teacher inscribes the quote cards with non-verbal behavior that often results in misunderstanding. The teacher can take inspiration for the non-verbal behaviours from critical incidents. The teacher can then inscribe these critical incidents in the quotecards. \n \n ● Step 2: The quote cards should consist of non-verbal behaviours from the different cultures represented in that multicultural classroom. \n \n ● Step 3: The teacher then divides the students into small groups, with each grouprepresenting students from different cultures. \n \n ● Step 4: the teacher introduces the students to the concept of the Iceberg metaphor (APA, 2021). \n \n Activity 2: Knowledge acquisition process \n \n ● Step 1: The teacher shares the quote cards to the individual small groups. \n \n ● Step 2: The students are instructed to read the cards and sort them into categories of their choosing. \n \n ● Step 3: Once sorted, each group must then name the categories as either acceptable behaviour or non-acceptable behaviour) explain the reasoning behind their choice. \n \n ● The teacher points out how the categories fit within the iceberg. In the explanation, the teacher explains how nob-verbal behavior (attitude), is hidden underneath the iceberg and the verbal behavior is above the iceberg and why it is hidden. \n \n Activity 2 helps the students to become sensitive and aware of acceptable and nonacceptable non-verbal behaviours from different cultural perspectives. A possible outcome is that some students might develop empathy towards their colleagues from other cultures. This opens up the possibility for behavior modification (Apedaile & Schill, 2008). \n \n ● Activity 3: Behaviour Modification process Students are provided with conscious behavior modification tips by the teacher. Such tips include. \n \n Conscious relay of non-verbal communication: Apedaile and Schill 2008 suggest telling the student thus. “Be aware of your own non-verbal communication” (Apedaile & Schill, 2008). This enables the student to understand that others may neither understand nor be aware of the non-verbal behaviour he or she exhibits. Hence, polite verbal communication might serve a better purpose than non-verbal communication that others do not understand. \n \n Selective judgement of non-verbal communication: Apedaile and Schill 2008 suggest telling the student thus. “Be aware of others’ behaviours and how these affect you. Unexpected and unfamiliar non-verbal behaviours can cause strong responses at an emotional level. Resist the temptation to make hasty, judgmental evaluations” (Apedaile & Schill, 2008). This helps the student not to be alert in always trying to interpret allnon- verbal communications. \n \n Conscious behaviour modification. Apedaile and Schill 2008 suggest telling the student thus. “Try to match your behaviour to those of the culture you are interacting with”. This involves the integration of the foreign student to the culture of the host country. The teacher should also inform the student thus,“Changing how you behave and how you understand others’ non-verbal communication is the key to successful non-verbal communication across cultures” (Apedaile & Schill, 2008). \n \n Do note that the onus for behaviour modification is on the student. The teacher only raises awareness.]]></string>
    <string name="tool_implementation_n_n_step_1_the_teacher_makes_the_choice_of_the_topic_of_discussion_for_the_student_a_critical_incident_that_has_cultural_undertones_is_a_good_choice_for_a_topic_n_n_step_2_the_teacher_divides_the_students_into_small_groups_of_at_least_2_students_n_n_step_3_the_teacher_instructs_the_students_on_the_following_rules_of_engagement_the_rules_stated_below_are_as_proposed_by_dresdner_2021_n_n_o_listen_with_openness_suspend_your_judgments_and_biases_and_listen_for_those_things_with_which_you_agree_as_well_as_those_you_might_challenge_n_n_o_listen_with_curiosity_engage_your_desire_to_learn_rather_than_to_try_to_fix_anything_n_n_o_listen_without_asking_questions_that_interrupt_the_speaker_jot_down_your_questions_and_save_them_for_later_n_n_o_listen_for_patterns_and_for_what_is_not_being_said_and_finally_q_n_n_o_listen_with_intention_what_do_you_intend_to_learn_or_do_with_the_information_you_ll_learn_n_n_source_of_quotes_dresdner_2021_things_to_note_for_the_students_as_proposed_by_dresdner_n_n_o_each_person_must_speak_once_before_anyone_can_speak_a_second_or_third_time_n_n_o_if_someone_asks_a_question_someone_else_must_answer_it_before_another_comment_can_be_made_n_n_source_of_quotes_dresdner_2021_n_n_step_4_the_teacher_should_identify_a_group_leader_who_will_ensure_that_the_rules_are_followed_n_n_step_5_as_one_student_in_the_group_speaks_on_a_topic_the_others_have_to_listen_attentively_and_intentionally_n_n_step_6_when_the_first_student_is_done_speaking_another_can_ask_a_follow_up_question_or_raise_comments_about_what_s_he_heard_n_n_step_7_steps_5_and_6_are_repeated_until_every_student_in_the_group_has_spoken_at_least_twice_or_for_a_specific_amount_of_time_n_n_step_8_the_group_leader_appointed_by_the_teacher_earlier_with_assistance_from_the_group_members_summarizes_the_conversation_and_identifies_patterns_or_insights_that_emerged_and_developed_in_the_course_of_the_dialogue_n_n_dresdner_2021_notes_that_teachers_should_not_be_alarmed_if_students_find_it_difficult_to_repeat_what_they_heard_in_context_from_their_peers_here_the_teacher_serves_as_a_bridge_to_help_the_student_pinpoint_what_they_misunderstood_furthermore_this_activity_should_be_practiced_continuously_to_help_the_student_perfect_their_active_listening_skills">TOOL IMPLEMENTATION \n \n ● Step 1: The teacher makes the choice of the topic of discussion for the student. A critical incident that has cultural undertones is a good choice for a topic. \n \n ● Step 2: The teacher divides the students into small groups of at least 2 students \n \n ● Step 3: The teacher instructs the students on the following rules of engagement: The rules stated below are as proposed by Dresdner, 2021. \n \n o “Listen with openness: suspend your judgments and biases and listen for those things with which you agree as well as those you might challenge;” \n \n o “Listen with curiosity: engage your desire to learn, rather than to try to “fix” anything;” \n \n o “Listen without asking questions that interrupt the speaker: jot down your questions and save them for later;” \n \n o “Listen for patterns and for what is not being said; and, finally,Q \n \n o “Listen with intention: what do you intend to learn or do with the information you’ll learn?” \n \n Source of quotes: Dresdner, 2021. Things to note for the students as proposed by Dresdner. \n \n o “Each person must speak once before anyone can speak a second (or third) time”. \n \n o “If someone asks a question, someone else must answer it before another comment can be made”. \n \n Source of quotes: Dresdner, 2021. \n \n ● Step 4: The teacher should identify a group leader who will ensure that the rules are followed. \n \n ● Step 5: As one student in the group speaks on a topic, the others have to listen attentively and intentionally. \n \n ● Step 6: when the first student is done speaking, another can ask a follow up question or raise comments about what s/he heard. \n \n ● Step 7: Steps 5 and 6 are repeated until every student in the group has spoken at least twice, or for a specific amount of time. \n \n ● Step 8: The group leader appointed by the teacher earlier, with assistance from the group members, summarizes the conversation and identifies patterns or insights that emerged and developed in the course of the dialogue. \n \n Dresdner(2021) notes that teachers should not be alarmed if students find it difficult to repeat what they heard in context from their peers. Here the teacher serves as a bridge to help the student pinpoint what they misunderstood. Furthermore, this activity should be practiced continuously to help the student perfect their active listening skills.</string>
    <string name="tool_implementation_n_n_described_is_the_implementation_process_as_extracted_from_sarah_apedaile_and_lenina_schill_2008_n_n_activity_1_imagining_prejudice_n_n_step_1_ask_a_student_to_draw_an_alien_face_on_the_board_or_flip_chart_n_n_step_2_you_can_also_draw_the_alien_face_yourself_n_n_step_3_invite_students_to_describe_what_had_been_drawn_on_the_board_or_flip_chart_n_n_step_4_once_all_students_have_described_what_they_see_the_teacher_then_asks_the_following_questions_n_n_how_do_we_know_all_this_when_we_have_never_seen_the_character_before_apedaile_schill_2008_or_how_do_we_know_all_this_when_we_have_never_met_this_character_before_apedaile_schill_2008_n_n_then_ask_what_are_we_doing_apedaile_schill_2008_it_is_likely_that_a_student_will_identify_their_action_as_prejudice_if_no_student_provides_the_correct_answer_the_teacher_then_reveals_the_action_as_prejudice_n_n_step_5_the_teacher_then_explains_prejudice_by_exploring_its_latin_root_praejudicium_praejudicium_means_an_opinion_or_judgement_formed_without_due_examination_apedaile_schill_2008_the_teacher_then_asks_the_participants_n_n_has_anyone_ever_thought_or_said_something_about_you_that_was_not_true_apedaile_schill_2008_n_n_have_you_ever_thought_or_said_something_about_someone_else_that_wasn_t_true_based_on_the_person_s_appearance_origin_sexual_orientation_apedaile_schill_2008_n_n_activity_2_imagining_stereotyping_n_n_step_1_the_teacher_then_asks_the_participants_to_think_about_the_character_s_neighbourhood_or_planet_pretend_that_everyone_in_the_neighbourhood_is_exactly_the_same_and_share_their_thoughts_on_what_they_think_about_the_imaginary_neighbourhood_n_n_step_2_after_students_share_their_thoughts_the_teacher_then_ask_this_question_based_on_the_thoughts_shared_by_the_students_n_n_what_are_we_doing_when_we_say_this_being_one_of_the_answers_given_by_the_student_it_is_likely_that_a_student_will_identify_their_action_as_stereotyping_if_no_student_provides_the_correct_answer_the_teacher_then_reveals_the_action_as_stereotyping_the_teacher_explains_what_stereotyping_is_and_proceeds_to_ask_the_participants_about_their_experience_with_stereotyping_they_could_be_the_stereotyping_they_experienced_or_that_which_was_directed_at_a_group_of_people_or_individuals_from_a_particular_culture_n_n_activity_3_imagining_discrimination_n_n_step_1_the_teacher_asks_the_participants_to_imagine_that_the_character_drawn_on_the_flip_chart_or_board_comes_into_class_and_the_students_refuse_access_to_the_character_as_a_result_of_their_culture_race_or_religion_the_teacher_then_asks_what_is_that_it_is_likely_that_a_student_will_identify_their_action_as_discrimination_if_not_student_provides_the_correct_answer_the_teacher_then_reveals_the_action_as_discrimination_the_teacher_explains_what_discreamination_means_and_proceeds_to_ask_the_participants_about_their_experience_with_discrimination_they_could_be_the_stereotyping_they_experienced_or_that_which_was_directed_at_a_group_of_people_or_individuals_from_a_particular_culture_n_n_activity_4_exchange_of_experience_n_n_step_1_as_a_facilitator_share_stories_of_prejudice_discrimination_and_stereotyping_that_you_have_experienced_and_how_you_felt_this_is_necessary_to_enable_the_students_to_open_up_to_share_their_experience_n_n_step_2_ask_the_students_to_share_their_own_stories_of_prejudice_discrimination_and_stereotyping_and_how_the_felt_during_the_experience_this_should_not_be_a_shaming_experience_for_any_student_n_n_step_3_a_good_way_of_wrapping_up_the_session_is_to_read_the_local_charter_of_rights_and_freedoms_to_the_students_it_is_good_practice_to_ensure_they_have_a_copy_n_n_it_is_important_that_the_teacher_is_conversant_with_the_level_of_language_proficiency_needed_by_their_learners_in_order_to_gain_the_most_benefit_from_this_activity_apedaile_schill_2008"><![CDATA[TOOL IMPLEMENTATION \n \n Described is the implementation process as extracted from Sarah Apedaile and Lenina Schill (2008). \n \n Activity 1: Imagining prejudice \n \n ● Step 1: Ask a student to draw an alien face on the board or flip chart. \n \n ● Step 2: You can also draw the alien face yourself. \n \n ● Step 3: Invite students to describe what had been drawn on the board or flip chart. \n \n ● Step 4: Once all students have described what they see, the teacher then asks the following questions, \n \n “How do we know all this when we have never seen the character before?” (Apedaile & Schill, 2008) or “How do we know all this when we have never met this character before?” (Apedaile & Schill, 2008) \n \n Then ask, “What are we doing?” (Apedaile & Schill, 2008). It is likely that a student will identify their action as “prejudice”. If no student provides the correct answer, the teacher then reveals the action as prejudice. \n \n  Step 5. The teacher then explains prejudice by exploring its Latin root praejudicium. Praejudicium means an opinion or judgement formed without due examination (Apedaile & Schill, 2008). The teacher then asks the participants: \n \n “Has anyone ever thought or said something about you that was not true?” (Apedaile & Schill, 2008) \n \n “Have you ever thought or said something about someone else that wasn’t true, based on the person’s appearance/origin/sexual orientation?” (Apedaile & Schill, 2008). \n \n Activity 2 Imagining Stereotyping \n \n ● Step 1: The teacher then asks the participants to think about the character’s neighbourhood (or planet!); pretend that everyone in the neighbourhood is exactly the same and share their thoughts on what they think about the imaginary Neighbourhood. \n \n Step 2: After students share their thoughts, the teacher then ask this question based on the thoughts shared by the students: \n \n “What are we doing when we say this (being one of the answers given by the student)?” It is likely that a student will identify their action as “stereotyping”. If no student provides the correct answer, the teacher then reveals the action as stereotyping. The teacher explains what stereotyping is and proceeds to ask the participants about their experience with stereotyping. They could be the stereotyping they experienced or that which was directed at a group of people or individuals from a particular culture. \n \n Activity 3: Imagining discrimination \n \n ● Step 1: The teacher asks the participants to imagine that the character drawn on the flip chart or board comes into class and the students refuse access to the character as a result of their culture, race, or religion. The teacher then asks, “What is that?” It is likely that a student will identify their action as “discrimination”. If not student provides the correct answer, the teacher then reveals the action as discrimination. The teacher explains what discreamination means and proceeds to ask the participants about their experience with discrimination. They could be the stereotyping they experienced or that which was directed at a group of people or individuals from a particular culture. \n \n Activity 4: Exchange of experience \n \n ● Step 1: As a facilitator, share stories of prejudice, discrimination and stereotyping that you have experienced and how you felt. This is necessary to enable the students to open up to share their experience. \n \n ● Step 2: Ask the students to share their own stories of prejudice, discrimination and stereotyping and how the felt during the experience. This should not be a shaming experience for any student. \n \n ● Step 3: A good way of wrapping up the session is to read the local charter of rights and freedoms to the students. It is good practice to ensure they have a copy. \n \n It is important that the teacher is conversant with the level of language proficiency needed by their learners in order to gain the most benefit from this activity (Apedaile & Schill, 2008).]]></string>
    <string name="tools_description_1"><![CDATA[The teacher’s goal in using this tool is to develop the intercultural competence of students. The tool enables the teacher to deal with challenges related to misunderstanding of cultural disposition towards others, asymmetric communications and differences in cultural behavioural norms. \n \n The setting for the implementation of this tool is a multicultural classroom and the students have to be clustered in multicultural groups for the activity. \n \n The teacher decides the duration and the resources needed for the activity. This demands creativity and innovation on the side of the teacher. \n \n TOOL DESCRIPTION \n \n The Jigsaw classroom method involves dividing the class up in groups of five or six students. Each member of a group is assigned some unique, cultural information of one of the student groups, to learn that must later be shared with the other members of that group in order for the group to achieve its common goal (Aronson & Patnoe, 2011). Such information could be on the asymmetric communications etc as mentioned earlier. An example of such information could be on “conversational norms”. In sum, this offers the opportunity for cooperative learning about a particular culture. \n \n USEFULNESS OF THE TOOL \n \n This tool helps in fostering cooperative learning in classrooms (Santos Rego & Moledo, 2005). It has been used to promote intercultural attitude and behavior of students in multicultural classrooms (Santos Rego & Moledo, 2005). The tool enables students in multicultural classrooms to acquire knowledge and skills relevant for them to work together without friction in multicultural groups. \n \n REFERENCE FOR THE TOOL: \n \n For more information about the tool visit: https://www.jigsaw.org/]]></string>
    <string name="tools_description_2">The teacher’s goal in using the tool is to develop the intercultural competence and global citizenship competence of the students. The tool enables the student to deal with all the challenges mentioned in module two, chapter one. This is because the self-reflection process results in the foreign student developing his or her cultural self-awareness to their host culture within the context of the challenges mentioned in module two, chapter one. In the process, they gain new understanding on how the wider world works within the context of their host. \n \n The setting for the implementation of this tool could either be an activity such as a seminar, a workshop or group activity within a multicultural classroom. The teacher decides the duration and the resources needed for the activity. This demands creativity and innovation on the side of the teacher. \n \n TOOL DESCRIPTION \n \n The implementation of this tool requires a book that describes what it means to integrate into the host society. Prof. Maura di Mauro has implemented this tool in Italy using the book “Feeling Italian”. The self-reflection tool consists of a list of 10 questions, which enables foreign students to become self-aware of the Italian cultural environment they find themselves. The tool implementation will be based on the Italian example. A teacher in any other country can contextualize this tool in their local culture, using a similar book from that culture. \n \n USEFULNESS OF THE TOOL \n \n This tool enables foreign students to conduct a self-assessment of their level of integration in the host society. This tool enables the student to develop further their cultural awareness to the host society. The tool also enables the student to understand how the host society operates in terms of cultural values, philosophy and norms. \n \n REFERENCES TO THE TOOL \n \n For more information, read: Self-Reflection Assignment based on Feeling Italian book by Prof. Maura Di Mauro – Intercultural Management Università Cattolica del Sacro Cuore, Piacenza. \n \n https://centerforinterculturaldialogue.files.wordpress.com/2021/02/icd-exercise-2-dimauro. pdf</string>
    <string name="tools_description_3">The teacher’s goal in using the tool is to develop the intercultural of the students. The tool enables the student to deal with all the challenges mentioned in module two, chapter one. This tool also aids in the students to gain knowledge that will influence their intercultural skill and attitude towards persons from other cultures. The difference between this tool and tool number two is that students actually go out to explore intercultural problems. Such problems could be any of those mentioned in module two, chapter one. \n \n The setting for the implementation of this tool is within and outside the multicultural classroom. The students receive instructions on how to implement the tool from the teacher in a classroom. However, they explore the problem outside the classroom in clusters of multicultural groups. The teacher decides the duration and the resources needed for the activity. This, as in the previous tool, demands creativity and innovation on the side of the teacher. \n \n TOOL DESCRIPTION \n \n One approach towards developing the intercultural self-awareness of students is to explore issues related to other cultures represented in the class. Students can be involved in small research groups where they have to investigate a certain issue through a small cross-sectional research project. Examples of topics that could be researched include differences in pedagogical approaches in their country of origin as opposed to their host country; the role of informal education in a particular culture; and or cultural communication patterns. After researching the topics, the students can produce interactive presentations as well as document what they have learnt in the process. \n \n USEFULNESS OF THE TOOL \n \n This tool enables the student to develop cultural sensitivity and cultural awareness via collaborative cross-sectional research. They can conduct the research by either reviewing literature or reaching out to persons from the target culture to interview them. Unlike the Jigsaw classroom, this activity goes beyond the boundaries of the classroom.</string>
    <string name="tools_description_4">The teacher’s goal in using the tool is to develop the intercultural competence of the student. The tool helps students recognize and to do away with stereotypes. The tool is very helpful for dealing with challenges arising from misunderstanding of cultural disposition towards others. These are challenges that could arise as a result of ethnocentrism, stereotyping, etc. The setting for the implementation of this tool is within and outside the multicultural classroom. In the multicultural classroom, a separate hour for the activity within a course should be set aside, if it is to be implemented within a course. The implementation of the tool outside the classroom could be in the form of an intercultural competence workshop or training session. \n \n The teacher decides the duration, scope and the resources needed for the activity. However, the teacher should ensure that students are provided with writing materials for the exercise. The teacher should also provide a white board or a marker for illustrations. The teacher can also decide to be creative on how to approach the interaction. \n \n TOOL DESCRIPTION \n \n This tool provides a 4-step process that enables students to unlearn cultural stereotypes. The 3-step process enables the student to become self-aware of the stereotypes they possess; evaluate the extent by which they stereotype; and make a conscious effort to avoid stereotyping. This tool only works if the student is willing to let go of cultural stereotyping. If the student is unwilling to make an effort, then this tool is not relevant. Howard, Ross, a diversity-training consultant developed this tool. \n \n USEFULNESS OF THE TOOL \n \n This tool is relevant in a class where cultural stereotypes and ethnocentrism exist. The tool assists the student to become self-aware of his/her cultural stereotypes and to unlearn these stereotypes. \n \n REFERENCE TO THE TOOL \n \n For more information: See . \n \n https://culturalmisconceptions.wordpress.com/2013/03/22/overcoming-cultural-stereotypes/</string>
    <string name="tools_description_5">The teacher’s goal in using the tool is to develop the intercultural and global citizenship competence of the student. The tool is suitable for dealing with the challenges outlined in module two, chapter one. The tool provides the knowledge needed by students to understand not just persons from other cultures but the culture of the person as well. The tool also enables the students to develop their intercultural awareness and sensitivity competences. \n \n The setting for the implementation of this tool is within a multicultural classroom. The teacher determines the duration of the activity. However, 45 minutes is ideal. \n \n The resources needed for the activity includes a book consisting of very short stories about a particular culture or nationality. The book should be available for all students in the class. \n \n TOOL DESCRIPTION \n \n This tool enables dialogue and exchange between students. It enables students to understand how their peers from different cultures feel, reflect, interpret and evaluate a single story. The group of students who use this tool will get to learn new words, grammar, narrative structures; understand the life experience of their peers from other countries, cities, places, people etc; and reflect on their life. The students will learn via self-reflection and active listening. \n \n USEFULNESS OF THE TOOL \n \n This tool developed the Intercultural awareness and cultural sensitivity of students. It also helps the student to learn about as well as understand the wider world. Furthermore, it helps the student to understand how to interact with people from different cultures. \n \n REFERENCE TO THE TOOL \n \n The tool is extracted from Bupnet.eu</string>
    <string name="tools_description_6">The teacher’s goal in using the tool is to develop directly and indirectly the intercultural and Neighbourliness competence of the student respectively. The tool is suitable for dealing with the challenges outlined in module two, chapter one. The tool exposes students to cultural differences using critical incidents that could prevent neighbourliness because of lack of cultural sensitivity and awareness in a multicultural classroom. The setting for the implementation of this tool is within a multicultural classroom. The teacher decides on the duration and resources needed for the activity. \n \n TOOL DESCRIPTION \n \n This tool was developed at the University of Illinois. It consists of a set of critical incidents used in order to understand the reasons for misunderstanding between multicultural groups. The instructor inorder to simulate real life conflict incidents that depict the source of conflict in multicultural groups uses the critical incidents. The lessons from the simulation helps students become self aware and knowledgeable of the behaviour patterns of other cultures. Thus reducing misunderstanding and providing room for neighbourly initiatives based on the knowledge acquired from this tool. \n \n USEFULNESS OF THE TOOL \n \n The tool is useful in preventing or solving conflicts that arise as a result of either lack of cultural awareness. The tool also breaks down the barriers that impede acts of Neighbourliness in a multicultural classroom. \n \n REFERENCE TO THE TOOL \n \n The example extracted from the developers of the tool is meant to serve as an inspiration in the simulation process. For more information about this tool, see \n \n https://apps.dtic.mil/dtic/tr/fulltext/u2/704517.pdf \n \n https://www.norquest.ca/NorquestCollege/media/pdf/centres/intercultural/CriticalIncidents Booklet.pdf</string>
    <string name="tools_description_7"><![CDATA[The teacher’s goal in using the tool is to develop the intercultural competence of the student. The tool is suitable for dealing with the challenges pertaining to prejudice, sterotypes and discrimination. These challenges could be as a result of any of the problems outlined in in module two, chapter one. The developes the sensitivity of students toward prejudice, sterotypes and discriminative behaviours they exhibit either consciously or unconsciously. The setting for the implementation of this tool is within a multicultural classroom. The teacher decides on the duration. In principle, this is not an activity that should take more than an hour. However, there could be circumstances due to class size where it might take longer to implement this tool. Hence, the teacher can use his or her discretion. To implement this tool, the teacher has to provide, the following: \n \n  Flip charts \n \n  Drawing materials (pens, board markers). \n \n  Local charter of human rights and freedoms. \n \n TOOL DESCRIPTION \n \n The aim of this tool is to enable the student’s self-awareness and implications of sterotyping, predjudice and discrimination (Apedaile & Schill, 2008). A fictional character and a cultural identity is used. In order to enable the tool to achieve its objective, the teacher should be aware of the level of trust they have from the students and adapt the exercises to suit them to avoid offending some students. \n \n USEFULNESS OF THE TOOL \n \n This tool will assist students in becoming self aware of the meaning and implication of stereotyping, prejudice, and discrimination. It is useful in the development of cultural sensitivity of students. However, this tool should only be facilitated by teachers who themselves are culturally sensitive to avoid chaos. \n \n REFERENCE TO THE TOOL \n \n For more information on this tool, visit: \n \n https://www.norquest.ca/NorquestCollege/media/pdf/centres/intercultural/CriticalIncidents Booklet.pdf]]></string>
    <string name="tools_description_8">The teacher’s goal in using the tool is to develop the intercultural and global citizenship competence of students. The tool is suitable for dealing with challenges emanating from the misunderstanding of verbal and non-verbal cues in the course of an interaction in multicultural classrooms. \n \n The setting for the implementation of this tool is within a multicultural classroom. The teacher decides on the duration. Just as is the case for tool 7, this is not an activity that should take more than an hour. The resources needed are quote cards inscribed with non-verbal behavior from different cultures. \n \n TOOL DESCRIPTION \n \n This tool educates the students on how to avoid misattribution, sending the wrong signal, missing reading body languages and the misunderstanding of context arising from non-verbal communications. The tool promotes behaviour modification based on knowledge acquisition. \n \n USEFULNESS OF TOOLS \n \n This tool will be useful in equipping students on ways in which they can gain knowledge as well as modify their behavior in order to transmit decodable verbal cues and decode other verbal cues. The tool will be useful in reducing conflicts that arise as a result of non-verbal communications in student groups in a multicultural classroom. It also helps the willing students to develop their global citizenship competences. \n \n REFERENCE TO THE TOOL \n \n For more information on this tool, visit \n \n https://www.norquest.ca/NorquestCollege/media/pdf/centres/intercultural/CriticalIncidents Booklet.pdf</string>
    <string name="tools_description_9">The teacher’s goal in using the tool is to develop the intercultural and global citizenship competence of students. The tool is suitable for dealing with challenges related to language barrier. However, the tool is only useful if the parties involved can sustain conversation in a common language. In this case the language of the host culture. The setting for the implementation of this tool is within a multicultural classroom. The teacher decides on the duration and the resources needed in the implementation of the tool. \n \n TOOL DESCRIPTION \n \n This is a tool developed by Lisa Dresdner, Ph.D.From Norwalk Community College (Dresdner, 2021). This tool enables students to develop their active listening skills. Active listening is an intercultural communication and neighbourliness competence. \n \n USEFULNESS OF THE TOOL \n \n The tool trains students to become active listeners. Active listening develops the student’s ability to pay attention to what their colleagues from other cultures say and not what they think their colleagues are saying. It is one way a student can learn about a foreign or local colleague from experience and not from a stereotypical point of view. \n \n REFERENCE TO THE TOOL \n \n For more information on this too, visit https://www.bellarmine.edu/docs/defaultsource/ faculty-development-docs/06-active-listening.pdf?sfvrsn=1db29481_2</string>
    <string name="tools_description_10"><![CDATA[This tool is different from the other. This is because it is a university initiative rather than an initiative a teacher can facilitate on their own. However, it is a tool that promotes the global citizenship of students. \n \n Using the Collaborative Online International Learning (COIL) model, faculties of at least two different institutions can partner to create joint courses, classes, or learning modules, to enhance students’ distant collaboration. For instances, universities can partner to create virtual learning activities, and to use common available social medias and exchange tools - such as Facebook, Google Groups, or discussion forum tools in the institution’s learning management system - to involve students of both institutions on topics such as diversity and social inequality (e.g., Kinginger, Gourvès-Hayward, & Simpson 1999; Liaw 2006; O’Dowd 2003; Thorne 2003; Custer, & Tuominen, 2017). Examples of students’ instructions are: write a 5+ line paragraph; present an example of how your society promotes particular gender roles in family and/or work, and explain how. Students can also be invited to attach visual “cultural” images that support, promote, and encourage the message they are presenting. Students of both institutions are then invited by their instructors to share what they wrote and prepared by using COIL modality. Instructors’ role during the virtual collaboration is to facilitate exchanges and discussions among students from different institutions, encouraging a cultural perspective understanding on global issues, and facilitating going beyond stereotypes and prejudices.]]></string>
    <string name="offline_tools_title1">TOOL 1. (Offline Tool) \nJIGSAW CLASSROOM</string>
    <string name="offline_tools_title2">TOOL 2. (Offline Tool) \nSELF-REFLECTION ASSIGNMENT BASED ON FEELING ITALIAN BOOK</string>
    <string name="offline_tools_title3">TOOL 3. (Offline Tool) \nSMALL RESEARCH GROUPS AND ETHNOGRAPHIC INTERVIEWS</string>
    <string name="offline_tools_title4">TOOL 4. (Offline Tool) \nOVERCOMING CULTURAL STEREOTYPES</string>
    <string name="offline_tools_title5">TOOL 5. (Offline Tool) \nSTORYTELLING USING SILENT BOOKS</string>
    <string name="offline_tools_title6">TOOL 6. (Offline Tool) \nTHE CULTURAL ASSIMILATOR</string>
    <string name="offline_tools_title7">TOOL 7. (Offline Tool) \nIMAGINING “PSD”: RELATING PREJUDICE, STEREOTYPE, AND DISCRIMINATION (PSD)</string>
    <string name="offline_tools_title8">TOOL 8. (Offline Tool) \nACTIVITY TO LEARN ABOUT CULTURAL NON-VERBAL COMMUNICATION CUES</string>
    <string name="offline_tools_title9">TOOL 9. (Offline Tool) \nACTIVE LISTENING: SMALL GROUP ACTIVITY</string>
    <string name="offline_tools_title10">TOOL 10. (Offline Tool) \nCOLLABORATIVE ONLINE INTERNATIONAL LEARNING (COIL) MODEL</string>
    <string name="material1">“Neighbourness” competences: A literature Review Report – WeLearn Intellectual Output 1 / Activity 1</string>
    <string name="material2">Intercultural Communication and Neighbourness Training Toolkit</string>

    <string name="online_tools_title1">TOOL 1: (Offline Tool) \nHow to be a_________? </string>
    <string name="welearn_website">&lt;u&gt;WeLearn Website&lt;/u&gt;</string>
</resources>